Hey, I have something I have to tell you guys.
It is not easy for me to do.
It's something I've been keeping inside of myself, locked up for a long time.
But today I woke up and I figured it's time for the truth to come out.
So I will be telling you the truth of what's going on.
You hear that sound?
I never opened the can in my life.
It's all at the press of a button.
You hear that?
It's been a lie all along.
No, I'm kidding man.
I recorded it earlier.
Here comes the real one.
You ready?
There it is.
Imagine
if that was true though, wouldn't that be the funniest, like, I don't even know, conspiracy of all time.
I don't believe you anymore.
No,
unless I can open it in the exact same manner.
You got me, Walter Whiteheads.
You know what's funny?
When you say that, I know exactly what you mean.
You know, it's awesome.
Demon behavior.
Remember this guy said he didn't like potatoes.
I do.
I love potatoes, guys.
It was real all along.
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding.
Dude, I'm doing great, Lymanate.
How are you doing?
I can't wait to play more Neutron, man.
I'm in a fantastic mood today.
You know why?
Because I'm healthy.
I am full because I ate a little bit of food beforehand.
It's Friday and there's Neutron.
Does it get any better?
I don't think so.
Oh, man.
What a time to be alive.
I can't do that accent.
My name is Dr. Caro Shortknife, I eat.
I think I'm pretty good at pronouncing the name, even though I'm not so sure.
Okay.
Um, it's Neutron time, baby.
Let's see if I can launch this shit without having it crash on me.
Neutron.
Okay, no crash yet.
What if I press this button?
Aha.
So far, so good.
Nice.
Okay.
Hopefully, that's not gonna crash later.
We'll have to see.
First crash doesn't count.
Amazing.
Palicado, been watching your Minecraft streams and as a long time Minecraft player, they're very fun.
I'm glad you enjoyed them.
Man, I'm going back to Minecraft.
And I don't want to say soonish, but almost soonish.
Because I want to play it again.
In fact, I've been playing a little bit off stream with a friend of mine named Kate.
Just doing some very basic stuff.
We made a small house inside a mountain.
It was fun.
Off spec.
Congrats on the blind win.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate it.
I'm actually not going for wins anymore.
Right now, I'm just going to become powerful and then explore as much as I can.
I want to explore everything there is.
Well, as much as I can.
Within reason, of course.
Oliver, can I tell you something crazy going on in the Neutron community right now?
Yes, tell me.
As long as it's no spoiler, go for it.
Of course.
I'm also nostalgic about Minecraft.
Isn't that weird?
Like I played it just recently.
It hasn't even been that long ago.
In fact, it was this year.
So weird how I feel nostalgic about it already.
I like you got your first win.
Congratulations.
Congrats on that.
How did it feel?
Hey, Cube Mill.
Hello, Oliver.
Finally catching a Twitch stream after binging your videos for a year.
Hey, man.
Welcome.
Glad to have you.
How you doing?
There's someone who's been doing a run for four months and is planning on staying on the same run for at least 500 hours.
Holy shit.
That guy is nuts.
Whoever that is.
Thanks.
Also, thank you Saltlap or Saltlap.
I don't know how to pronounce your name.
Thank you for resubscribing for three months now and Ujuri as well at two months.
I really appreciate it, guys.
66 viewers.
That's so demon.
It's actually not demon yet.
We need only 600 more for that.
Oh, it's Furyforged.
Oh, yeah.
I know about that.
Someone told me last time.
I thought it was someone else.
He was actually in this chat a couple of streams ago.
Now I feel kind of... what do you call it?
Backwards awestruck or like starstruck.
You know, like in the past starstruck.
If that makes sense.
Because that guy must be really good at Neuter to be that far in the game.
Holy shit.
Hats off to that guy.
Okay.
How's everybody doing on this Friday?
Huh?
You guys have any plans for the weekend?
Or just chilling?
Also, I need to turn off this music.
Please don't crash on me.
Do not crash on me.
There we go.
Nice gentle wind.
You're going to IKEA with your family.
Good luck not getting lost.
Depends on the IKEA.
Some of them are designed in a way where you get lost easily.
Others are really nice to navigate.
By the way, just wanted to say, because I missed the TV conversation, Severance is amazing.
Maybe the best show I've seen.
Other people suggested Severance as well.
So it's on my list for sure.
But thanks for the suggestion, Liminal Roar.
I have watched True Detective season one and I fucking loved it!
So good.
Great season.
Loved Matthew McConaughey and also I forget the other guy's name.
The Redhead.
God, what's his name?
You know who I'm talking about.
You're gonna freeze four kilos of strawberries, Isansi?
Why?
Just chilling?
I like it, Elavie.
Chill on, brother.
You woke up for the stream, so still kind of asleep but getting better?
Hey, what time is it at your place?
D&D with the boys?
That sounds fun.
And just chilling, watching you gonna play Neutel later.
That sounds like a day.
Lovely.
Might watch some of the Olympics.
Oh, is that on right now?
I didn't realize.
I'm happy because I've been seeing my friends a lot lately.
That's nice, man.
I'm so happy for you.
Chill one for you, smelly, Ellie.
Busy week, so can't wait.
I know that feeling.
Trust me.
That's the best thing about Friday.
It's knowing that the week is over and it's time to chill.
So nice.
Lord Eternal, doing good.
I've got blueberries, raspberries, goldfish, soup, jelly, potato chips, and dip.
And licorice boats for snacks today.
Going pretty good.
Man, I'm jealous.
I like all of those things you just mentioned.
Although licorice boats, I'm not sure sure what that means, but licorice, hey, I'm in.
My favorite is jungle roll.
Probably none of you know that, unless you're from Sweden or Denmark, I think.
Oh, opening ceremony tonight.
Ah, I see.
You like succession?
I love succession.
One of my favorite shows ever.
Yeah, I'm a huge movie slash show fan.
Love talking about that stuff.
Anyway, I gotta play this game.
Look at this.
It's beckoning me.
Okay.
I was in the middle of a great run, wasn't I?
Well, I wasn't that far, but it was promising.
I'm gonna close you guys down.
Hold on.
Let's move this mouse over here.
Guys, thank you for showing up and chilling with me right now.
I'm just gonna kick back, relax, drink some of this coke, and enjoy this beautiful Friday with some good old gaming.
See you on
the top with the music.
Wand experimenter.
That's been carrying me hardcore.
Let me take a quick peek in here.
What have I done?
What do I have in here?
I need to be digging.
I have black holes, teleport, and all seeing eye.
Okay.
It's coming back to me.
Did I use any healing?
I did not.
Okay, good to know.
Good to know.
I guess because I have the tinker healing.
Tinger tinger healing wizard.
That did not have the same mouth or like sound feeling as tinker tinker soldier spy.
Now, what is it with these statues?
Why is that guy's head a book?
Is that Gorb?
A big kahuna burger.
If any of you get that, you're a real OG.
Uh, hold on.
There's a wand over there.
There's a guy there.
I need to see.
Okay, so I have this sick looking wand.
Very cool.
I have add manas that I didn't add because they add a bunch of castellae.
That's right.
Okay, it's time to rock and roll, bitches.
Melee immunity, tinker with wands everywhere.
I have to remember that I can do that.
Good.
Let's go.
I do seem to remember having better digging though, but I guess I could use the black holes.
Oh, will you please destroy that piece of land right there?
Hold on, I have to adjust the volume.
There we go.
It's a bit too loud for me.
Okay, here we go.
I do remember this wand not doing exceptional damage.
Wasn't there a spider that came into the holy mountain and I tried to kill it and it took forever?
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, let's be careful here.
Let's be careful.
That guy has a wand!
Always scary stuff when they have a wand.
What is it?
Holy shit!
What's that?
Heavy shot?
Greatly increases the damage done by a projectile at the cost of its speed.
Oh, 0.30 though.
Oh, interesting.
A lightning thrower.
Okay, hold on a second.
Let me see.
Oh, let me see how much of an impact that actually has.
Like, what is the feeling of it?
Cost seven mana.
Adds a bit of cast delay as well.
Oh, okay, okay.
Probably does way more damage though, right?
I wish I had one more speed up.
That would be cool.
I don't think it's worth it at this time.
Or is it?
Hold on.
Nah, I don't think so.
I will keep it on the standby for now.
Wait, trifurcated?
Hmm, let's keep that one and keep that one.
The rest... Oh, also, how's this wand?
I have to remember what kind of wands I have.
0.08, 0.27.
The crazy part is I can edit my wand anywhere.
It's kind of insane.
No, throw the wand away, I think.
Just put this wand on the floor.
There we go.
I extracted the most valuable stuff from it.
If I find more speed up, I can circumvent the issue with the slowdown on the heavy shot.
That's the plan.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I almost forgot, I almost forgot.
We got to shoot this wand.
Because we have healing on it.
No, wait, why is there no healing now?
Oh, maybe I can't change it.
Okay, that's actually good to know.
If you remove spells from a wand you just found, it will not heal you anymore when you use it.
That's kind of important.
Good thing I just tested that.
Okay, and we do not have water.
We have worm blood and purifying powder and water.
I should replace the purifying with water.
Also, how do I get in there?
Of course, with that.
Nice, money situation is kind of not the best.
There we go.
What's this?
Green glimmer?
What does that do?
Oh, that actually just reduces castellate.
That is not bad.
Hold on.
Let me try something.
Also, let's... Oh, I forgot.
Wait, I need to shoot it.
Ah, I'm an idiot.
Yeah, shit, I forgot to fire it first.
Crap.
I just told myself.
Oh, man.
So if I put this here... Oh, it's... Wow.
Hold on, that's a huge change.
Look at that.
Maybe now adding mana will do the trick.
It looks kind of cool too.
It's all green and shit.
Man, that little bit of castellate is really changing a lot, huh?
I'm not sure if this is better or not.
We're gonna have to try it.
I'm not sure.
I think it's actually a little bit worse.
But if I remove this, I think it's better, just in general.
It shoots fast, but it also runs out of mana fast.
That's some burst.
Okay, don't switch out spells.
Start using it.
There we go.
Look at that.
Full healing.
In fact, maybe I'll just keep some of that.
Horizontal.
Yo, that's not bad.
Removes castellate?
Adds damage.
Yo, that is kind of sick, right?
Hello?
Wait a minute.
Also, what does this do again?
Removes recharge time and castellate.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, but wait a minute.
This puts it on a horizontal path.
But I have an idea.
Watch this.
I'm gonna...
If I do this, and I just add it together, wait, where did I put my...
So this is a mod... If I put this at the end, what does that do?
Okay, so it does it like that.
If I do this, it's the same.
Can I somehow make it not... Oh, that's funny.
I think it's because this one... So it shoots this spell, right?
What is the next spell?
This one.
But it's a modifier.
And what does it modify?
The next spell in the sequence, which is...
That one.
That's why it shoots both.
See?
Kind of cool, honestly, but not really what I'm looking for.
Recharge time.
Wait, is that one unlimited?
No, not in that case.
But if I add mana like this...
No, definitely not.
Okay.
All right, we're still gonna rock that for now.
Cool.
Get rid of that.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no!
Oh, shit!
This is scary.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That is a scary spell, man.
All the damage.
Whoa.
Let's teach this guy a lesson, huh?
Didn't even die from that.
All right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck me.
God, that's annoying.
That's really annoying.
Got him.
Oh, hold on.
I actually want this back.
You know, I should start using this, uh, like, everywhere, basically.
I mean, I only have 10 of them right now, but may as well use it, right?
That's actually kind of scary.
I should not do that.
I should not teleport into the unknown.
It's a bad idea.
You know, I may actually prefer my wand without this for now.
Uh, let's get rid of that one.
Like, it shoots a little slower, but that's okay.
All right.
I just don't like running out of mana.
It's just not, it's not very cool.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Sick start to this.
That feels great.
What's this?
A spell refresh.
Wait, what?
Look at it.
There's a spell refresher behind here.
What the fuck?
Okay.
Uh, you know what, actually?
I am gonna switch over to this.
I'm actually gonna write that down.
I'm gonna have a, uh, notes.
Oh, let me make that a bit thicker.
For current run.
I'm just gonna have, like, a spell refresher
in jungle right side.
Just for future reference, because say I find some, uh...
Uh, well, basically, if I need to refresh anything like healing or something, right?
I can come back here.
That's actually a big deal.
How do I sort of signify that it's here?
Maybe I put a spell here to make it obvious.
Let's put something I won't miss.
One black hole.
There we go.
It's right next to the black hole.
That's what we're gonna say.
Okay.
We got a mine.
Goodbye, sir.
Whoa!
Oh, no.
Who's shooting that?
Is that you?
That's so annoying.
Oh, my God!
Stop it!
Why is this blood not working?
What?
Okay, that made no sense to me.
It's almost like I made it worse by, uh, using the worm blood.
Is that what happened?
Weird.
Uh-oh.
There's someone there.
Look at that.
Oh, is that a dead spider?
I'm not so sure.
Oh, man.
They have some HP.
I am scared about them.
Get rid of that guy.
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
He's spawning them!
Oh, I hate it.
Also, I hate this bugging thing going on there.
Oh, no.
I'm actually in trouble here.
I'm poised.
Stop poisoning me!
Oh, it's going terrible.
Get in the blood.
We need water ASAP.
Did he just spawn another guy that spawns another guy?
100 HP.
Oh, no.
Please don't die like this.
We gotta take stock here.
Calm down.
Just calm down.
Maybe I should go heal.
I could... You know what?
I'm gonna go heal.
I should not take any chances.
I just feels bad to do it, you know?
But I guess that's what you gotta do when you fuck up like this.
Actually, hold on.
There's a wand right in there.
How about we get in there?
What's that?
Metal?
Say, what?
What the fuck is that?
You see this?
Like a chandelier.
Uh-oh.
Just kill that dude.
Kill that dude.
And now we heal.
Okay.
Thunder charge.
A projectile with immense... Wait a minute.
This is bad.
I'm not sure I trust this man.
So this is gonna... Okay, this is no shuffle.
It's gonna cast Downward Slarpa.
And this... I can't remember whether or not this one explodes right at my feet or not.
I don't trust it.
I'm gonna go up and heal.
I'm a pussy.
I'm gonna grab that wand and I'll try to heal when I'm at like 70% or something.
But other than that, no.
I just don't want to die like an idiot right now.
That would be the worst.
Got it.
Okay.
Let's move on.
So I will just remember if I need to heal, there's some stuff up here.
Oh, we need to grab water.
Let's get rid of this.
In fact, put it in here.
Purify it.
Yeah, there we go.
Replace that.
Lovely water.
Very good.
Let's take it easy.
You're dead.
Ah, we got another wand.
Oh, wait, there's mushrooms.
Should we get high?
We could... Oh, I'm scared of these mages, by the way.
Bombs.
Okay, that's easy.
That's an easy heal, if we need to.
You know what?
Let me use this.
Oh, yeah, it's so good.
It reveals dangers and shit, of course.
Pheromone.
Water everything.
I'm already out of water.
Hold on.
That's no bueno.
Uh, why didn't we have a big pool of water somewhere?
Is it over here?
Ah, I'll take that blood.
That is just as fine.
I mean, it doesn't convert toxic shit, but it's better than nothing.
Okay, I'm in no rush to go through this level, by the way.
I am taking my sweet time.
I want to explore everything.
Because that also means finding more wands, which means finding more potential healing.
For later.
That was smooth.
Oh, nice!
Come on, guys.
Very good.
Oh, let me grab that blood.
Now I also crit more.
Spiders down there.
Oh, it's so creepy the way it moves.
Especially when it's in these tight corridors and the legs are like on the walls.
Oh, man.
Nasty stuff.
Hate these guys.
At least I can shoot this wand for a pretty extended duration.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, we're fine.
There's a flower.
Kill it.
Just kill everything.
That is the motto in this game.
If you're not sure what it is, fucking kill it.
Would be nice to have the freezing spell right now.
Just for the AOE.
Oh, no, he spawns spiders.
No, wait, he actually spawns random enemies, it seems.
He's gotta be dead now.
Nope, not yet.
There we go.
I feel like my game is slowing down again.
It's weird that it's doing this.
It hasn't been... Oh, wait, is it just me who's slow?
No, no, it's definitely slowing down.
Look at this.
Ah, slugging.
Ah, what's happening?
It hasn't been doing this for like 50 hours and now suddenly I get it quite frequently.
I do wonder why that is.
This guy needs to be taken care of immediately.
See, I hit something there.
I think there was a frog down there.
Okay, I'm gonna go back up.
Whoa.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'm immune to melee.
I actually kind of forgot about that.
So they're not gonna hurt me.
I mean, unless they start to bleed lava on me.
Which is another problem in itself.
Is this where the worms come?
Yep, kill them.
What was that thing I just hit?
Nice.
Let's explore the top part first.
Oh, there's a spider.
I thought it was a laser pointer.
Damn, my dude was stuck.
Somehow I just gained a shit ton of gold.
Like I was at 300 when I started.
Now I'm at 1700.
Dude, the black hole is nuts.
Quantum split.
I think I had this before.
Makes a projectile split into three projectiles.
Whose existences are entangled.
176.
You know what?
Let's try that.
Let me actually experiment with that a little bit.
Oh, I should shoot it first.
I'm an idiot.
I forgot it.
It's over.
Never mind.
I can't heal anymore now.
I had my shot.
Makes a... Oh, this one is sick, but it only has 10 charges.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm busy here.
Hey, guy, come here.
This is scary.
Fire everywhere.
Bro, I'm so tired of you.
Holy crap.
And he opened access to this place.
That is fine.
Right.
I wanted to try to do...
Throw that away.
Man, why is my game so laggy?
It doesn't feel good, man.
This is...
I feel like it's running super slow.
Am I imagining things?
Maybe I am imagining things.
Let me try and put this on here.
Yo, hey.
That looks pretty dope, doesn't it?
Hold on.
I need to see this again.
Modifier makes a projectile split into three projectiles.
Whose existence is...
Notice how it starts a little bit into the shot.
Like here.
You notice how it splits off here and not at the beginning.
That's dope.
And hold on.
It also adds 0.08 cast delay.
So if I add this now, is that enough to make it sort of sustainable?
Uh-oh.
Okay, not bad.
Not bad.
Yo, that's actually not bad at all.
I like it.
In fact, look at that.
I think we're limited by recharge right now.
So if I add this...
No?
Uh, double?
That's even better.
Right?
Hold on.
We gotta test this.
Let's see how much damage we do.
Why is it so quiet suddenly?
Oh, the music is gone.
That's what's doing it.
Come on.
One enemy when you need one.
Please.
There we go.
I'm not sure, honestly, about the damage here.
Does that make a difference at all?
It doesn't, actually.
Oh, it actually does.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
That looks insane.
I think I like it.
But I'm not 100% sold on it, you know?
So what I'll do, I'll put this stuff on this one for now, because I actually really like that wand.
And then I'm gonna exchange this wand with... Hold on.
I'm gonna grab this spell and put it on.
Which wand do I like more?
This one or that one?
I think I like this one more.
Even though it, nah, casts two spells per.
I don't like that.
Maybe I'll take this.
I'll keep the one I have.
Thank you.
There we go.
Okay.
That looks insane.
Let's just get a feel for it.
We gotta kill some enemies with it.
Because at this point, things are shooting so fast, I honestly can't tell whether or not what I'm doing is an upgrade or not.
Maybe I'm making it worse, you know?
It's really hard to tell.
I gotta feel it.
Get it in my system, in my bones.
See, that's a bad idea what I just did.
Don't ever do that.
I don't know why I did it.
I feel like I'm doing more damage.
We got another book, book man.
Oh, I thought that was alive.
What is going on with this statue?
Notice how it has this finger down here, or the hand, and we know there are enemies that have these hands.
I wonder if this is somehow significant.
Maybe if I lure one of those enemies here.
Oh my god, that log is tripping me out.
Ah, don't like that.
Oh, ooh.
Nooky lair?
No, thank you.
I think I'll stay clear.
A mysterious darkness lingers in this place.
See the... Oh, wait a minute.
Did you see the little clouds on either side of that message?
I wonder if that means we see those clouds in there again.
The impossible to deal with clouds.
I don't want that.
I'll come back here later.
Let me write that down.
Because I really want to explore that place to the full, you know?
I'm just too scared when I'm not powerful enough.
Explore...
Ah, all right.
Kind of want to dig through here.
Oh, notice how when I'm shooting close quarter, the quantum stuff never actually happens.
You see that?
But if I shoot at long distance, then they fuck around.
So yeah, definitely activates later on.
Oh my God.
What's that?
Oh, it's a flower.
Bro, call me crazy, but is it the sliminess?
I just feel like my game runs slow.
This does not feel like normal slime.
Look how slow I am.
It could be the slime.
I'm actually not sure.
Is the game rendering slower than normal?
Okay, I don't think it is.
I think it's honestly just me.
I'm being kind of idiotic right now about this.
The slime is really messing with me.
Uh oh.
Anytime I see one of those mages.
See, right now I don't have any slime on me and it's so slow.
Look, look, look.
It's slow motion.
I need to start over.
There's something wrong with my game.
I can't play like this.
This is weird, man.
I wonder if it's something I have running in the background.
Hmm.
I'm gonna lock in again.
See, now it feels right.
You see that?
Oh yeah, much better, much better.
Oh yeah, it's snappy now.
Hopefully it stays that way.
I'm not crazy.
I felt it.
Hello, sir.
Oh, I can't dig through that?
Okay.
But watch this.
Ah, sick.
These guys again.
Is that oil?
It is.
Ominous liquid?
I hate that.
Ominous liquid is bad.
Oh, please die, sir.
Give me that money.
Ah, that was a bit close.
Ominous liquid is just pure damage, right?
Yeah, don't go in here.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not brave enough.
We're coming back there later.
Yep.
I kind of want to find a small teleport bolt.
I'm not a big fan of the long teleport.
I think I'm doing less damage with this wand.
Also, no, no, no.
Okay.
It looks more crazy, right?
Something's going on in there.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Yeah, I'm not sure I like this one.
I think I'll change it back.
Maybe we can use this one for something else later.
For now, though, put all of this down here.
Remove that.
Wait,
what did I do?
What did I do?
I'm missing something.
What am I miss?
Oh, wait, it's the wrong one.
I'm an idiot.
There we go.
Back to normal.
The other thing about the teleport wand, when it's the long teleport, it's varying how long it takes for you to get teleported away.
You can't be consistent with it, you know?
Because if I shoot straight up right now, it's going to take like one or two seconds before I get teleported until the bolt hits something.
But with the small one, there's always an upper limit on the timer, you know?
That's a big deal.
Okay, we got a portal here.
Very cool.
Lost a bit of HP here.
We need to find a wand.
Actually, we do know that where there's a wand, we could go heal with it.
Let's do it.
We're playing safe today.
I'm not taking any chances here.
And we'll, we'll even explore a little bit on the way there.
Wait, do I have... Oh, I'm twitchy.
Okay, let's just wait a bit.
Actually, it's not that bad that I'm twitchy with this wand.
Ukuskivi!
Maybe I want to pick that up, actually.
Thank you.
Maybe we can use it somehow.
Also, I need to fix this.
Change this around.
There we go.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
That is a enemy?
It is not.
I think it was up here.
Uh, no, where the hell was it?
Well, I haven't explored here, so that's fine.
Well, there's actually something going on there.
Doink!
Motherfucker.
What's that?
Levitation.
Come on, worm!
Wanna dance?
I have no idea where this wand is.
See, this is the kind of spot where I should be using this.
To see if it's even worth digging.
Maybe you see something in there.
Maybe not.
I think it's up here.
There it is.
That's the wand that we're looking for.
Oh, wait, this is the scary one.
I wanted to find the other one.
But you know what, fuck it, let's try it.
We're not gonna die from one hit of this anyway, right?
Let's see.
It shoots one shot, so that's something.
Boink!
Holy crap!
Wow!
Okay, it casts copies of itself, so never mind.
But let's keep healing.
Oh, I hit myself with it.
Yeah, this is bad.
Maybe if I do it over here where I'm...
Okay, that's better.
It's only when it hits something.
Okay.
Not bad, not bad.
I actually kind of like that.
Okay, crazy, crazy idea here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, we're gonna change it.
What is this thing right there?
Why is it shaking?
Hmm, very intriguing.
Ah, there's that other wand.
Let's just heal up.
Then we bomb the shit out of things and then in the process.
Oh, I'm out.
Oh, but it still heals, look.
That's funny.
So if I find the empty wand somewhere, I wonder if that's even possible.
Then it will still heal, it just won't do anything.
Okay.
No, don't throw blood in there.
Silly goose.
A ghostbuster.
I can get to him.
Let me in.
Okay.
I will say the other one that Quantum Splits is a bit easier to use when dealing with these small animals that just go everywhere, like this guy.
It's because it splits off, you know?
Bigger AOE.
The game is slowing down again.
I don't understand what's happening.
I wonder if it's something related to... I'm trying to think what it could be resulting after all my time playing.
Earlier save files maybe?
If they don't get cleaned up or something?
I'm not sure how it works, but maybe that's going on, you know?
I don't know.
Because I'm trying to understand why this never happened in the beginning and why it's happening now.
I had a wand here.
I think we tried that one already.
Let's head west.
In fact, I'm going to go down.
When I head west now, I'm going to go to the entrance to the Loki lair and then just go down.
Yeah, I remember this now.
So down here, for example.
Yeah, here we go.
Oh, someone's in there.
There's a single pixel.
I can't get rid of it.
That's so annoying.
That's the Loki lair.
Let me just take a quick peek.
Here's what I'm wondering though.
So I am good on HP right now and I actually do have melee immunity.
Spiders do melee damage.
So I'm thinking there's got to be big rewards in there.
So maybe we do go in there.
Oh, no, no, wrong one.
I was going to shoot, not teleport.
But look at these guys.
Oh, my God.
Blood me.
Okay, we're fine.
That was a bit of a disaster there.
I got one of them.
Look at them digging.
Okay.
Am I immune?
Let's just quickly double check.
Yeah, I am.
Look.
Beautiful, beautiful stuff.
Beautiful stuff.
I couldn't remember whether or not it was all spiders or just some of them because I remember there being different kinds.
Let's just get rid of that.
It won't explode on us later.
All right, fuck it.
I'm going in.
No fear.
Maybe we'll even find ones we can use to heal with.
If things get too dicey, we get out.
It's that simple.
You got to be brave, right?
Although this oil makes me uneasy.
Oh, I've been here.
Okay, so hold on.
This is what I'm going to do.
Watch.
Aha.
Oh, it gets unrevealed afterwards.
That's weird.
Huh.
Is that specific to this place?
Because I don't feel like that's always been the case with that spell.
Yeah, this is especially dark.
Oh, I see a guy over there.
Oh, no, it is those things.
So you can kill them if they're not too close.
It's the problem of getting in melee with them, then.
Wait a minute.
Are they hitting melee?
Because maybe I'm immune to their damage.
I'm not sure, actually.
That guy right there.
Oh, shit.
That's where it came from.
Maybe the only survival strategy in here is to get high as fuck.
Eat all the mushrooms.
I don't like ominous liquid.
Can I turn ominous liquid into something else?
Uh, I don't like this guy.
He was shooting some kind of thing at me there.
Oh, yikes.
Let's go.
What's that?
I think it's a torch.
Oh, God.
But I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Yo, what?
This guy ain't dying at all.
I don't understand.
Huh?
I do nothing to him.
Maybe there's like a damage threshold that if you don't do enough damage per shot, it doesn't penetrate.
I'm okay.
You know what?
No, no, no.
We're coming back later.
I need I need no, I don't like the fact that I can't kill them.
That is just not something for me, man.
That's nope.
Them being spiders is enough.
Unkillable on top of that, even though they can't kill me.
No, thanks.
Makes me very uneasy.
But I'm not done exploring.
In fact, I know there's a boss in here, and I'm pretty sure I can kill it.
Although I'm not entirely sure.
My one is not amazing.
So maybe I shouldn't take the chance, now that I think about it.
Uh, get through here.
Who's in here?
Okay, I'm not scared of you.
You can't hurt me.
Everything is Gucci.
I'm slimed up again.
It's actually such an annoying debuff.
Takes forever for it to go away, too.
Nice.
I actually got a lot of money.
What is going on here?
Why are there eyes in there?
Is that gold or ice?
Is there a spider embedded in the ground?
Oh, what the fuck?
Look at us.
That is nasty.
Okay.
Oh, I see you.
Dodged.
Easy.
Wait, what the fuck are you doing here, guys?
What's happening?
Oh, there's a wand.
The wand looks big.
Oh, hold on.
There's a guy up there.
No, use the wand.
Get rid of that shit.
I do wonder if this toxic shit is going to disappear.
Pinpoint of light.
Electric arc.
It shoots four spells.
That explodes after a moment.
I think I can heal with that, but I got to be careful.
So the way this is going to work is that I shoot it.
It's going to shoot it off in random directions around me.
And after a while, they're going to explode.
So I need to be... also, they have arcs between them.
Oh, no.
This could be bad.
Try it.
Holy shit.
Yeah, we're not doing that.
This one goes bye-bye.
See ya.
Nope, we're not trying that again.
That was way too crazy.
Holy crap.
What?
Why did it keep going like that?
Man, that was scary.
The wand looks cool, though.
It's bigger than me.
It's like a spy hunter.
Let's go all the way to the right now.
Right, there's the spell refresh.
Put it next to the black hole.
It's an odd place for it, too.
Look at all this growth.
Why am I in here?
Good question.
I do not know.
Ow.
Don't get slimed up now.
Aha!
Let's see.
Short range homing.
It's healing.
This is a definitely okay-ish healing.
Hold on.
Did I just...?
Okay.
Heal me up, Scotty.
You like bombs?
Wow, the chance of him running into that bomb at that moment.
Amazing.
I do not want that worm on the loose, though.
I guess I should have thought about that before I did it, huh?
Heal up.
There we go.
That was the last one.
Where did my wand go?
Wait, that's another wand.
Oh my god.
Excuse me.
What the fuck is happening?
Oh, it's you.
I thought it was raining bombs.
Couldn't understand.
Okay, easy healing.
Ooh.
Hello.
Look at the stats on this bad boy.
That's not bad at all.
Nice.
Good healing there.
0.12.
Honestly, I... hold on.
I actually like it.
Let's put this here.
Now put this in this one.
Exchange these and throw this one away.
I want to keep this one.
Just for the spells.
It'll be my... you know, I can actually use these to teleport or like transport spells, I guess.
Right, whatever.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's my all seeing eye?
Where did I leave that?
I think I left that with a wand down here somewhere.
Yeah, I picked up a wand here.
It must have fell down.
Wow, it fell.
Huh?
Where did it go?
Someone must have picked it up, maybe.
Hold on.
We're playing detective now.
What happened to my wand?
Last time I couldn't find my wand, I was killed by that wand a couple seconds later.
So I'm extra worried about it.
I think someone took it.
Some of these enemies picked it up.
Someone is off having a giggle with my wand.
Look at all this damn blood.
Feels like I almost have verta, verta, verta on, but I don't.
Okay.
Oh, is that my?
No, that's just a bit of fire.
Yeah, I have no clue what that wand is.
It is gone!
Hopefully I'll find it.
Oh my god, that guy is doing damage.
He's the same guy that killed me when I was in that pyramid temple thingy.
On the ground, remember?
Really cool place, by the way.
I gotta go back there.
But the poison was just killing me in that place.
I was not prepared for that at all.
It was a major disaster.
Wait, sweet.
Now, I want to do this.
What's in here?
Jesus!
There we go.
It's like cutting through the jungle with a machete here.
Thick.
What's up here?
Why is that so odd looking?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
Big plant.
Show me the goods, game.
Are we here?
This is the spot.
I don't know if I can do it, though.
I'm scared.
Cluster bolt.
This wand, it's... how much?
I think this guy had like a thousand HP or something, right?
This is not hitting for that much.
I feel like I don't trust it.
Let me walk around a bit more and maybe find a better weapon.
Or, I mean, some way to make my wand even better, you know?
And then I'll come back.
Oh, here we go.
Bro!
Talk about Schlaraffenland.
Earthquake.
I really like that one.
Chain bolt, large fire bolt.
Magic.
I actually don't like any of these.
Is that crazy?
I mean, I like this one, but it's limited because I don't have an unlimited spells.
I don't like it, but I can use it to heal, I guess.
It's gonna throw four randoms.
That's gonna be death, isn't it?
Is that too risky?
God damn it.
This is the ultimate wand experimenter.
Ah!
Yep.
Okay, okay, man, okay, okay.
I have learned my lesson.
If something looks crazy, don't do it.
Just don't do it, man.
Don't do it.
That's number 68, baby.
Wow.
Hold on.
I gotta open a window real quick because I'm dying in here.
One sec.
Ah, there we go.
Much better.
I was actually dying.
No, I'm better.
Well, I died in the game, but also in real life, you know?
Okay.
We're back.
Let's go.
Oh, that works.
That's fine.
Eh, eh, eh.
There we go.
Ah, barely.
Hmm, I can probably make that.
Just stand like here.
Ah, fuck.
Okay, okay, fine.
Come on.
We got this.
There we go.
Man, what a death, huh?
I can't believe that actually killed me.
Like, I expected to maybe take some damage, but not instantly be killed, so that was honestly a bit of a surprise.
Oh, nice.
A single hit.
Not bad.
That means I have 13 left to explore with.
Actually, a decent start.
I don't like that I have polymorphine, though.
That's terrible.
Don't get near that.
In fact, I don't like that it's just sitting there.
Makes me nervous.
BAM!
Damn.
We're back in the hemisphere, boys.
Back in the old hemisphere.
Whoa, did I just hit something?
Ah, probably not.
Okay, watch this.
This hemisphere is gonna be the smoothest and cleanest you've ever seen, okay?
It's gonna be quick, efficient, and delicious.
Just like a baked potato in the microwave.
How is this guy not dying?
Hello?
There we go.
What do we got here?
I hate that I'm starting with this spell, though.
It's my least favorite.
I mean, it works.
We can definitely kill people.
Okay.
Look at all that explosive.
Whoa.
Try by shooting.
This is a real action hero moment.
When you drop down in the air, you shoot in through here, you know?
Very nice.
Let's cut through here.
Aha!
I had a feeling.
Oh, can I not?
Hey!
Hallelujah!
Nice!
Real good.
Dude?
Oh, wait.
I don't have water.
Wait, I have an idea.
Watch this.
Check this out, check this out.
Oh my god.
Hey, sir.
Come on, come on.
Hit it, hit it.
Step in it, step in it.
Step in that sweet... Come on, you fucker.
Step in it.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, dude.
I almost put polymorphine on myself just now because I thought it was water.
Oh, I'm dying here.
I'm actually dead.
Look at the amount of fire it's on me.
I have no water, it's over.
Emmis!
Get out of my bath!
Ah, there we go.
Much better.
Let's get rid of this shit.
We need pure water.
That's the only way forward.
Having polymorphine in here is just a bad time ahead.
Especially when your muscle memory is to click that button whenever you're on fire, you know?
Okay, fill up the bottle.
But I feel like my strategy was good there.
If he had only stepped in that shit, I could have one shot him after.
Oh, I want to blow that up, but I also kind of don't.
Let me go teach the guy a lesson now.
Now that I have water, will that do the trick?
He's an absolute menace.
See, I'm scared about all this polymorphine on the ground here.
It makes me uneasy.
Put water here.
Maybe just ignore him.
What's that?
Unstable teleportation.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'm actually going to pick that up.
Because first of all, it's in a bunch of water and I can fill up my water bottle.
Second of all, I need to figure out what the difference is between unstable and stable teleportation.
So if I find a teleportation bottle, I will be comparing them.
Oh, grab water, of course.
Here we go.
Nice.
Full on water.
That's what we like.
I keep wanting to change to my second one to teleport.
But I can't do that, of course.
Okay.
I could get through here, but let me first check down here.
Oh, what the fuck is happening?
There's two of those guys there.
This game is not going easy on me right now, huh?
Let me go another way.
Oh, oh, oh my God.
And this guy,
it actually doesn't get worse.
This is pure.
Torture.
Ah, I see HP though.
Reward for my troubles though.
Thank you.
That worked.
In fact, why don't I just use my TNT to kill those fire dudes?
There's another one.
Actually unreal.
Hey dude, I know you like fire.
Hey.
Oh, now he's bleeding loud.
It's bad.
Good thing about the bouncing shot is, well, it bounces.
How are you not dead?
There we go.
Water it.
Sweet.
Not bad, actually.
I feel like I dealt with that quite well.
What's up here?
Hey, horta.
Yo, did it just skip across the water?
I thought it just skipped like a stone on water, you know?
Like skipping stones.
If the angle of attack is small enough.
Oh, there we go.
It's one time, baby.
Hopefully we get something good.
Imagine if we... Dude, it's even possible to find healing on a wand in the first level.
Imagine.
How crazy would that be?
Okay, I guess I gotta cut my way in.
That's fine.
I still have some bombs left.
A black hole!
Oh, and the wand itself is not bad either.
Pretty dope.
I like it.
What do we got here?
Just a bunch of toxic sludge.
Oh, another wand.
Circle of shielding.
I can never remember what the difference is between that and stillness.
Is this the one that... Right.
Yeah.
You know what?
This is actually not a bad spell.
Think about all the times when it's like a goddamn bullet hell.
You know?
You stand there in your little fucking orb or whatever, and you just spam your spells and you stand your ground.
Because everyone who shoots at it, spells will get deflected.
Not bad, actually.
I need to start considering these things.
Uh-oh.
No!
I'm stuck!
Yeah!
There we go.
I really don't want to use more TNT to get through there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hey, sir.
That was a good hit.
Yeah, going the acid!
Let's just take damage from that.
Execute.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, look at that, look at that.
What was in there?
That was a bomb in there.
Hahaha, yeah.
Don't trust these chests, man.
Just don't.
Do not trust these chests.
Now this guy...
Wow.
Almost got me.
I got you first, though!
Money.
Ah, more HP.
This is actually a sick run so far.
Surprisingly, this is very difficult, but also very rewarding.
Right?
I just had a genius idea.
What if I lure him up into my little bath?
I'm gonna run him a bath, and then he's gonna jump up here after me.
Come here!
Come get your bath!
There's a bit of lava there.
I see it.
Don't like that.
Jump in the bath!
He doesn't want to, he doesn't want to have his bath.
That's fine.
Are you like that?
Hey!
Hahaha!
Sometimes you gotta force it a little bit.
If the cat doesn't want to go in the bath, you gotta bring the bath to the cat.
That's something our forefathers used to say.
It's really not, though.
I made it up.
That's right.
I lie.
Okay, I'm gonna go up here.
Oh my god!
Guys, this is nuts!
Oh, dude.
I just had a great idea.
We have black holes, we go in the dark cave, we heal.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
See, this is the situation where you die.
These guys, and you're in a tight corridor.
Because you have no space to dodge.
That's how you deal with it.
Stay out of range, hit him good.
Wait, I'm out of water!
Oh, that's bad.
We gotta find water immediately.
This is actually an emergency.
Water is so important at this point for me that if I don't have water on me, I stop everything I do and get water.
I know it sounds a bit overkill, but guys, if I catch fire now, it's over.
Should I really be taking his bath water?
Yeah, it's kind of nasty.
Maybe don't go that way, I've already been.
Yeah, I want to go this way.
Yo, look at that.
Isn't that kind of neat, the way that's upside down triangle?
I think I like that a lot.
Man, where was this big basin of water that I found?
Was it up here?
Oh no, not this polymorphine bullshit.
Here we go, there's the water.
And there's so much of it too.
Kind of want to get rid of the unstable teleportation just to have two bottles of water.
Is that crazy?
Maybe.
Now we go back.
Smooth operator.
Dude, I'm not actually... Here's the thing about Neuter.
I'm not even mad or like disappointed about dying just before in that other run.
Honestly, I didn't like my wand that much anyway.
But of course, there was good potential to make a good wand because I had all these nice perks, right?
But still, every time you die, immediate thought is, ah, chance to start even better, you know, to make something even better this time.
And that's what I'm gonna do.
We're gonna make something crazy happen this run.
Mark my words.
You don't believe me?
Watch.
It's gonna be crazier than your wildest dreams.
Man, those things bounced like 10 times.
Okay, now that we have water, we continue our journey.
Uh-oh.
Just clear out everything.
Any enemies hiding?
Man, oddly quiet here, isn't it?
Makes me a bit worried.
Oh, here we go.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh no, you know what?
I may have changed my mind.
I feel like this may not be the best idea I've had.
Okay, new plan.
We're not gonna go to the cave.
Instead, because we're gonna save that heal for later, okay?
Instead, I'm just gonna see it this way.
We go to coal pits now, and we're gonna heal in there.
And then we're just gonna act as if that heal was the heal we got in the cave.
Nice.
Yo, teleport!
Ah, but it's not the small one, though.
That's okay.
Transmogrification.
That's actually sick!
I may actually get that.
Let's see what we got.
Plague rats, dissolved powders, projectile eater.
I don't particularly like any of those, so I may re-roll.
But first, let me see.
If I buy this, that, that's 90.
Maybe I get another dynamite.
That wouldn't be too bad.
And that's pretty much it.
That would be 110, so I still have a lot of money.
Okay, I'm gonna re-roll.
Never skip leg day.
Melee immunity is nice, although there's not that many enemies with melee attacks.
Is there?
Doesn't feel like it.
But I'm taking it.
I do like having spider immunity.
And then we go with this, that, and this, and also this, but also this.
Maybe a bit of...
That's it.
No, one more of these.
Okay.
Transmogrify that bitch right there.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, let's see how good it is.
It's decent.
It's not the worst.
Here, we're gonna put...
Uh, how good is this wand?
Yo, this wand is actually not bad.
We need to figure out... think about a damage wand first.
I mean, this is not great, is it?
But it kind of is what it is.
Fireball, no.
Yeah, my damage situation is bad.
Black hole is nice.
That one is actually dope.
I'm gonna put it on this one.
That's gonna be my transmogrify wand.
And then we have the teleport wand, the damage wand, and then we have a dynamite wand.
How do you like them apples?
Huh?
This cat costs one mana?
Maybe we'll put it on here, because why not?
It's kind of cool to have some light on it.
I like it.
All right, let's move on.
Oh my god, look at this shit.
Oh man, my damage is absolutely terrible.
This one sucks.
No thanks.
Uh, hold on.
Just bounces off that one.
I need to do this.
Whoops.
Aha, ukoskiwi!
Thanks.
Okay, I need to find a better wand.
Stat.
But, if I find a difficult enemy, it's transmogrify time, baby.
That's my strategy on that.
Oh, wands everywhere.
Hello.
Do I like it?
No, don't like it.
I do not.
Look at this stuff right there.
What?
Thought for sure that would at least set fire to this firecracker.
Ah, hold on.
Why, how did I?
Ah, here we go.
0.12, 0.7.
I mean, I think damage is pretty good on this.
200, 5, 2...
0.7.
Let's see it.
No, actually, I don't like it.
Switch back.
Nope, another wand.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Holy shit, that guy came blasting.
Damn, son.
Bro, bro, bro.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe it's time for this one, just for this guy.
Ah, there we go.
Hand it over.
A bunch of spitter bolts with timers.
I don't like it.
Oi!
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
What's up here?
A bunch of gold on the ground.
Ooh, look at that.
Acid and a lot of it.
I'm starting to think this is not a four.
It's just a random ass symbol.
It looks like a four, but I see it on every one of those.
So, you know, it's probably not a four.
Oh my god, I can't hit him.
There we go.
Okay, not bad.
Not bad.
Honestly, I don't really care about my shitty wand.
I found so much HP, I should be grateful.
And I am.
Hey!
Firebomb, that is infinite.
341.10, that is not a bad wand.
I would say it's better.
Even though it shoots kind of slow.
It's limited by recharge.
Whoa!
Oh no, oh my god.
Disaster hits.
Wow, suddenly everything goes to shit.
That's what's going on in Noita, man.
0.05, 0.43.
This wand is good.
It actually is good.
I should use this wand or take it with me at least.
Yeah, I'm actually gonna keep it.
I'm keeping it.
Like it needs one of those hits and that's nice.
I just need to be careful with my aim.
Dead rats!
Look at that.
I think I shoot the exact same projectile he shoots, which is kind of funny.
What's happening in there?
Why does that look like that?
Water me up.
That's the end of the line.
Okay, not bad.
I like it.
I need to take a sip here.
I
gotta remember I have teleport.
That's right, baby.
Uh-oh.
These guys are gonna be hard to deal with, I think.
No, never mind.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Didn't even die from that.
Are you still not dead?
You are dead.
Nice.
We have our exit, but I'm not satisfied.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh man, they explode before they hit that target too.
I didn't realize that.
Stuff is happening.
Oh, that dicks.
That's actually so good.
Oh, this is getting a little bit sketchy.
Ouch.
Oh, I just blocked that attack because I have melee immunity.
Oh, it's so hard to hit them.
Long distance is an issue.
This guy is somehow in the wall.
How am I gonna kill that guy?
Oh, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
Check this out.
That's how we do it.
Yeah, baby.
Yes, yes.
Oh, it's so good.
Beautiful.
Advanced strategy is coming out here.
Hello.
What do we have here?
Wait, why is that just there?
What?
All right.
Oh, he just died from fire right in front of my face.
Ambrosia potion in a very precarious spot.
I can get it though.
Watch.
We're digging.
I gotta be careful not to hit the... Oh, that's gonna be a little...
Ah, crap.
I knew that was gonna happen.
But all is not over.
I'm gonna pour this down here.
And then I'm gonna pick that Ambrosia up.
I feel like I should start using that more.
Mostly because I haven't actually used it at all.
Like, for reals, you know?
I realize what it does and I haven't really been abusing it.
Oh, yeah.
Give me that sweet.
It looks like whiskey.
Drinking it makes you sick.
Ambrosia.
I'm trying to understand what that word even means.
I feel like I've heard it before.
Like, not in the context of this game.
I mean, isn't that like a love potion?
Ambrosia?
I don't know why, but that's what my mind goes when I hear it.
Hello.
Whoa.
Yeah, we gotta turn you guys into sheep.
I just don't play like that.
I don't play like that.
I can get in there.
Ah!
Oh my god!
Bro, circle of transmogrification is actually one of the craziest bells in the game.
So good.
I'm draining the water.
Wow, it's inside a water reservoir.
Look at that.
What do we got?
A kind of shitty wand.
Yeah, I don't like it.
Do not enjoy that one.
Hello.
Now that's an upgraded TNT wand, I would say.
Yank.
Thank you very much.
Are you guys being spawned somewhere?
Who's your mother?
Who is your mom and what does she do?
Hey!
It's shuffled though.
I think I like it.
Oh yeah, it even digs.
Look at that.
Does this hurt me?
I'm not sure.
Powerful magical bolt.
Cool.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, it's definitely better than what I have.
Ah, it's so good.
Nice.
Okay.
Sometimes it shoots all three at the same time because of triple spell, other times it doesn't.
It's kind of funny.
Oh, what the hell?
How did I just catch fire?
Weird.
What do we got up there?
Oh my god, it's so good at digging!
What the hell?
Oops.
It's spraying lava everywhere.
There's a wizard here and I'm scared.
Wizard man?
I think he went down here.
Did he die?
Maybe he died.
Oh, we got the fungal caverns.
Very scary place, but also very rewarding, potentially.
Set this on fireplace.
There we go.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Question though, do I go in there?
There's a wand.
Let's check out the wand at least.
Oh man, it's already a mess.
Look at that.
Oh my god, this place is just the worst.
Maybe I don't do it.
What was that?
Reflecting.
Am I hitting myself with that?
I'm not sure.
I really need to figure out whether or not this, uh, magic missile or whatever that I have is doing self-damage.
Oh wait, I'm immune.
Hey, hey, hey.
Fuck yeah.
Of course that counts as immune.
I mean melee.
Uh, is that also immune?
Oh my god.
Guys, this is my moment.
It's time.
Finally.
This place is not a threat.
That's also, I'm also immune to this, right?
Yes.
Oh, that's just amazing.
Amazing.
Hey, come here fools.
Oh, I'm not immune to that though.
When they start shooting the green goo.
Nope.
Whoa.
Actually, oh my god, this one sucks.
Look at the mana recharge.
I didn't realize this until now.
Oh god.
This is a big oof, but I definitely want to keep it because the spells are good.
Just a bit unfortunate there.
Oh no.
Water me, water me.
There we go.
Guys, they
have just a lot of gold.
How are you?
Hey, motherfucker.
There we go.
He died at least.
That's something.
Oh, look at all that gold.
Oh, I missed it.
Shit.
It's okay though.
I should find concentrated mana.
That would be great right now.
In fact, I need more water.
Nice.
And here.
It's not going too bad, I would say.
Definitely getting saved here by... Oh, he has a wand.
Oh, that's the... he has pollen.
Oh, you can't shoot that far with it though, how can you?
It's annoying that I can't destroy those projectiles.
I wonder if pollen counts as melee damage.
Probably not, right?
I want that wand.
Yo, there he is.
Got him.
Let's see that wand.
Oh, look at all that.
Flammable gas.
It's gonna catch fire now.
Yep.
There we go.
In fact, I'm just waiting for this all to blow over there.
In the meantime, let's find a way into that wand.
Kick them, kick them, kick them, kick them.
The kicking doesn't work.
These guys at least, they're not susceptible to that.
Come on.
There we go.
Trust me, I would not be here if it wasn't for the melee immunity.
I would be gone.
Like the wind.
Okay, so the way to get in there is basically you don't get in there.
That's the, uh, the shortened end of it.
There is no way for me to get in there.
Not at this present moment.
There we go.
Uh-oh.
That guy's gonna shoot some stuff and I'm not gonna be happy about it.
So maybe I just give him a surprise present here.
Boink.
Uh, why are those so wild?
Oh, spiral cast.
I get it.
Oh, that's gonna take a while, isn't it?
Are you gonna melee me?
No, you're gonna poison me.
What's that?
Is that berserkium?
Hold on, let me grab that wand.
My god!
Nice!
This, oh, yeah, oh, I just fuck, I just remembered.
I have transmogrification.
Um, keep this one in mind.
Ah, broken wand!
Taking it.
And that is blood potion.
Okay.
It is blood.
Watch this.
This is how we deal with him.
Doing.
Easy mode.
In fact, I kind of forgot I had this.
I should have used this just before when I was in trouble.
Why didn't I remember that?
Would have made everything so much better.
What's this?
Oil potion.
I don't like oil.
I just, oh, look at that, a heart!
I'm being rewarded by my curiosity.
Well, not quite, but you know.
Another hidden wand there.
Well, not that hidden, but...
Watch this.
Choke point.
You guys like that?
Boink!
I only do one damage with the kick.
Is that gonna, wait, is that filled with helium?
Sweet.
Sweet Jesus!
Firebolt with trigger.
Another wand up there, too.
Man, this place is cool.
I like exploring this place with melee immunity.
That's actually...
Oh, man.
Okay, melee immunity, much better than I thought now.
Because now I know I'm immune to spiders and everything in here, almost.
You know?
Such a big deal.
Hey, come on now.
By the way, I'm shooting so slowly because look at my recharge.
I don't want to be spending mana too hard here.
And since I can't take damage from these guys anyway, I may as well aim my shots carefully.
I could get up here.
That thing's gonna explode in a second, I think.
We could start eating...
Book of Guidance!
I remember this!
I actually kind of want to read it again.
See, why is that in here of all places, right?
Makes you think.
That guy needs to die.
Okay, he made his way in.
He's so annoying.
It's wild.
There we go.
Nice.
Why did I lose HP?
Kind of want to get rid of... Oh, what's happened?
Oh, someone has a wand!
No, it's Ghostbusters shooting each other?
Guys, what's going on there?
Are you all right?
Watch me break up this party.
Yeah, you like that?
Have fun.
Nice.
So look at this here.
Upside down pyramid.
I need to grab some of this.
Oh, nice.
Oh, look at this.
Personal Fireball.
Wow, spread minus 23?
That means I have a lot of...
What do you call it?
It's free real estate, basically, when it comes to spells.
When the spell has a lot of spread, it will be negated by that.
Oh, look at that.
There's an Ukuskivi.
Let's free the water.
Freeze the water.
We got to eat some of this to get rid of it.
It's the only way, guys.
Let's see.
What does it say?
One of my brethren ran away in order to escape our predicament.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hid something here in this room, but I lack the ability to see what is here.
In this room?
Okay.
What does that mean?
There's a ball with... kind of looks like a rock, doesn't it?
Is there a puzzle here?
I'm not sure what's going on here.
Let's keep an eye on things here.
Keep an eye out for anything suspicious.
Wait, what just happened?
Oh, it disappeared.
Right.
It just takes a while for the circle of transmogrification to disappear.
We've got a dude up there.
Kind of want to mess with him.
They're all hidden away.
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
That's what I like.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's satisfying.
Oh, what's going on there?
You know what?
I'm going to open this.
Blow it open.
Yeah, we got to wait a bit.
That Ukuskivi is messing things up.
That's Berserkium too.
Hold on.
Yeah, that's a death trap right there.
Whoa.
Much better, much better.
It's still kind of scary, but it's not as scary.
Question marks.
I don't like that.
Question marks make me unhappy.
Doink.
Come here.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
You're mad now, bro.
Okay.
Polymorphine.
Slimy egg.
Like look at this one also has a four on it.
I don't think it means... Oh, actually, I went.
They do differ a little bit.
Oh, Invisiblium.
I think I like it.
Let's get rid of the Ukuskivi.
There.
Ah, it's this guy again.
My dude.
Let me go invisible.
Wait.
Oh, the Ukuskivi is messing with it.
Come on, Ukuskivi.
Get down there.
How scary are you, sir?
What kind of wand are you processing?
Oh, it's like a...
Oh, okay.
That's not too bad.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna sheep him.
Come here.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about, baby.
Burst of air.
I mean, boo.
Goodbye, sir.
There's also a wand here.
Kind of crap as well.
Don't want it.
Chest up there.
Two chests.
Now that's a lot of bombs.
Pretty dope.
There we go.
Cool.
Let's write that down.
So this is not the same run anymore.
We have to remember that.
So I have to delete some of these things here.
Special.
I need to make this way bigger.
What the hell?
Why is this so small?
I have the eraser equipped here, but it's way too small.
What the hell?
Oh, you don't have a better idea.
I'm just gonna do this.
There we go.
Delete it.
And then
spell refresher in... I guess fungal caverns is what it's called.
Fungal caverns.
Very nice.
That could come in handy.
Down the line.
Kind of want to get high.
Let's do it.
Eat all the mushroom.
See what's gonna happen.
I'm tripping balls now.
That should be enough, right?
Oh, I'm taking damage.
Oh my god.
I didn't even notice.
Oh no, I was just taking damage like an idiot.
Steam echoing and shifting in colors.
Steam, huh?
Hold on.
We can test this.
No, I picked it up by accident.
I didn't look where I was walking.
I was looking up here.
Dammit.
Oh well, whatever.
So if this water gets turned into steam, let's blow some of it up.
Shit.
What does steam become?
Smoke, maybe?
Did it get turned into smoke?
Ah, it's possible.
I'm honestly not quite sure.
Maybe the smoke is always there after a bomb.
Oh, wait.
Steam.
Wait a minute.
Am I not understanding something here?
What was this before?
I am not sure.
I'm not sure what that was.
Is it the other way around?
Have I been misunderstanding the way this works?
I think maybe I have.
Oh!
What?
Did I touch something?
Did I touch teleportation?
I must have.
Okay.
All right, then.
I guess I must have.
Weird.
Wait, there's nothing up there.
What's up, man?
Yeah, teleportation.
What is... Oh, it's a heart!
Holy shit!
I was like, something is vibrating there.
What is that?
It was a glorious heart.
Yeah, don't touch the teleportation.
Blood potion.
Whoa!
I hate these guys.
What are you going to throw at me?
I'm scared.
Ah, in fact, no, I am scared.
There we go.
That works.
Now, I'm going to find out what the secret is to that room up there with the Book of Guidance.
Another... Oh, I can get to that wand.
I can get to that.
Watch.
In fact, I feel like I've seen this exact thing before, where I went up on the right side.
Remember?
I tried to teleport up.
Am I crazy?
It's like the ultimate deja vu right now.
Huh.
No, thanks.
Kind of want to get high again.
Let's do it.
More.
Oh, yeah.
Eat it all.
We're tripping balls.
Here it comes.
Let's really keep an eye on what it says now.
Oh.
Wait, what?
There was no text.
Oh, I'm high AF.
Holy.
Oh, man, it's a ghostbuster.
What are you doing in the fungal caverns?
Oh, God, I'm puking everywhere.
What the?
What are you doing, my friend?
Oh, my God.
I can't tell what these things are.
What's that?
Concentrated mana.
Oh, nice.
I need that.
Let's not break it.
Let's throw away.
Oh, man.
Wait.
Wait, what just happened?
Oh, wait, what?
I'm so confused.
Oh, what's happening?
Why does it keep happening?
Something's going on.
I don't know what to throw away.
Maybe I'll throw away invisiblium.
Yeah, fuck that.
Let's grab.
No, I broke it.
Oh, man.
Oh, fuck.
What?
How?
Well, that sucks.
I can't get in there, it seems.
I need to dig a little bit.
I have bombs.
The spiraling does not help me here.
Oh, that's gonna blow.
That's gonna blow.
Let's be careful.
I think I killed that.
Horta.
Rocks.
Nice.
What's that?
Pheromone?
Sure, I'll take it.
Consolation prize.
Thanks.
Is the music also different now that I'm high?
It sounds more hippie.
If that makes sense.
Like, more trippy.
Like, a kaleidoscope right now.
Uh-oh.
Actually, I'm not scared of him.
There we go.
There we go, bitch.
Uh-oh.
I think they're still doing melee, those guys, so I shouldn't be too worried about them.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
There we go.
Yeah, I'm blocking everything.
How come the small ones don't get turned into sheep?
Maybe they need to be of a certain size for that thing to work.
There we go.
Very nice.
Get rid of all that.
Can't risk these explosions in my face.
This has been the most successful fungal caverns expedition I've done so far.
Mostly because I've been carried here by my perks.
Or should I say my perk, singular.
This is a fun run so far, man.
I'm enjoying this immensely.
Come here, you.
Ah, you're annoying.
Make me waste all my mana.
This is the worst.
There we go, there we go, there we go.
Okay, let's see what else we got in here.
All right then.
A shiny orb.
That thing will explode into money.
I forget how many kicks it is, but let's
not kick it too much.
Let's destroy it.
What if I kick it now?
Still works.
Yeah, cool.
Okay, we're out of the caverns, but I'm not done.
I am not done.
There's potentially gold in them hills.
I want to get in there so bad.
That want's gotta be good, right?
Can I not get in somehow?
Does this dig on metal?
No.
Unfortunately not.
That's a whiskey.
Oh, here we go.
Bone dust plus weird fungus pouch.
Sure.
I've been wanting to have one of these pouches again for a while.
In fact, let's try and pour some in here.
That does nothing.
We gotta try and pour that into everything.
Let's try the whiskey.
Mix it up.
Okay, maybe nothing.
All right.
I think it's time we head back into... Hold on.
Wait, did I not check this wand?
It's glowing.
Oh, I did.
Okay.
Uh, you know what?
No, I'm gonna leave that in.
I was tempted.
Uh, let's get high again.
Maybe you can only do this shit once.
Let's see if it happens again now.
There we go.
Diamond echoing and shifting in colors.
So I wonder, does that mean diamond shifted into something else?
Or did something random out there change into diamond?
That's what I'm not sure about.
I think it's the second option there, because uh, apparently steam is, uh, if steam, okay, if steam doesn't exist anymore, then I know it's the first.
Right.
Ambrosia.
Yo.
Hmm.
I changed my mind.
Fuck off.
Come with me.
There's actually stuff below me as well.
Oh, I'm an idiot.
I'm an idiot.
I didn't see that.
Shit.
Mistakes were made.
That was a bit of a bummer there.
I can't believe I did that.
Oh no, but it's fine.
Water.
First we water them.
There we go.
Mix it up a bit.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
And then we do this.
Watch.
Easy.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
Oh, okay.
What else is hiding down here?
Okay.
Nothing else.
I think it's time we go back to Coldpits now and explore some more there.
I'm kind of stuck.
There we go.
I guess I could just teleport out.
I forgot I had that.
Let's be extra careful.
Uh-oh.
These are the guys I'm scared of.
And of course, short shotgun people.
He's kind of short, I guess.
Don't shoot me.
I feel like I'm safer in the fungal cameras than I am out here.
Just because of the immunity I have.
That is actually real.
Am I squeezing the lemon right now too much?
Should I be going through that portal?
Uh-oh.
Don't you think about it?
What?
Oh, there was a bomb in there.
Yep.
Can't trust the chests.
Not all the time.
Oh, that guy.
I don't trust him.
Nice.
Huh.
What's going on here?
There's a shotgun man.
Scares me a little bit, honestly.
He died.
Nice.
Very good.
And there's a portal for us.
We could take it.
Wax?
There's a guy up here.
Oh, there he is.
I'm really proud of myself.
I feel like I'm playing really well right now.
I'm doing great.
Nice crit there.
60 damage.
Damn.
Sweet.
What is that?
Why is that blood white?
Eh?
What the hell's going on there?
That's weird.
Is it not?
I feel like that's weird.
Okay.
I think it may be time.
Was this unstable teleport?
I did that.
I remember pouring that.
Yo, wait a minute.
Why is...
Is this because of this?
Why is blood white?
Huh?
Let's go.
Weird, man.
Okay.
Well, let's see what we got.
Bunch of those.
Uh, okay.
Dynamite?
Hmm.
Not a big fan of any of these.
Fungal disease.
When near danger you sprout fungal growths.
Why is that good?
Why does that help me?
Cordyceps.
Fungal creatures spawned from the corpses of enemies killed by you.
Yeah, no.
I'm going to reroll this.
Pin pool.
That's nice.
Rage fuel, levitation, homing shots.
I don't like that.
Sometimes you don't want that on your spell and this is like permanent on everything you do.
I think I'm going to go with pin pointer.
Spells fly faster too.
Lower spread.
And I have this nice laser pointer.
Not bad.
I like it.
Okay.
So let's see here.
We can probably make something nice happen now that we have this amazing spell.
And maybe even just like this.
No, this one sucks because of the mana charge speed.
How about this one?
330.99.
102.34.
Nope.
It's got to be this one.
And we have an ad mana too, actually.
Oh, hello, actually.
Wait a sec.
Oh, no, no.
This is a shuffle, of course.
We don't want shuffle.
Like if I say do this.
Recharge speed is relatively low.
Wait, what?
Oh, no.
I forgot about that.
It cast this bullshit as well.
The spiral pattern.
Dang it.
That sucks.
But you know what?
We could do this and just throw this in there.
At some point it's going to shoot.
Actually, it's not fantastic either.
How about we use this one?
Let's just test a couple things here.
Too slow.
Too little mana.
Let's check the ones here.
0.07, 0.47.
That's a decent contender.
0.37, 0.52.
This is shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Yikes.
We got to go with this one.
Yep.
Give me that.
Which one do I want to replace?
Probably this one because it sucks.
I don't like the spiral pattern.
Spiral goes away.
There we are.
And then we even have some pollen.
Cool.
Three there.
And then we do...
Okay.
Running out of mana there.
So maybe instead of that we do
two with a mana on it.
Definitely much better.
I guess decent damage too, right?
But am I happy about it?
If only I had a bit more slots there.
This is the one with the shitty mana charge speed.
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna go with the double and the mana.
I think this is fine.
It's a decent one for now.
And then we can have a bunch of dynamites because that's fun.
We get to blow shit up.
And they should fly faster too, right?
Doesn't look like it actually.
Never mind.
Of course we need this.
And that's about it, I think.
Could be nice to have a couple black holes with us just to dig through something thick if we see it, right?
What is the next place?
It is the snowy place.
So the snowy place is a lot of open space, isn't it?
That should be okay.
A lot of snow.
We can dig through that with dynamite and this one.
I think we're good for now.
Let's move on.
Actually, wait a minute.
Were there any spells that I absolutely wanted from these?
I don't think so.
Maybe that one could be... Actually, this one is... I'm gonna buy it.
Fireball Orbit.
Let's try it.
So instead of that, we do...
Yeah, well... How much mana cost?
40.
Ooh.
Yo, isn't that kind of nuts?
Hello?
I wonder if that's good or not.
I'm actually not sure.
I don't know how much mana that does.
Let's try it.
Fuck it.
There's no reason not to try it.
And then in here, we're gonna have this wand back.
Actually, no.
Change it just so we don't have a shuffle wand.
I don't like shuffle.
Wrap this one.
Can
we put all of this on here?
There we go.
There we are.
Nice.
All right, let's move on.
Go.
There's always this little pool of water here.
Have you noticed?
That's the same every time.
All right.
I'm still not quite sure what the damage is on this bad boy, but let's just keep going.
Look how fast it shoots too.
Like, it's pretty much exactly where I aim.
All right.
This is looking good.
Looks like a great wand.
Oh, that's actually a decent one, except it only has two slots.
So not that great, actually.
And that potential, that's for sure.
Wow, everything dies in one hit.
That's actually surprising to me.
Where are you?
I heard you.
This is one of my favorite tracks playing right now in the game.
Really like it.
We can grab some more water here.
I'm kind of stuck.
Oh wait, that's actually kind of scary.
If I use this in close quarters...
Oh wait, the fireball doesn't... Oh, the fireball doesn't activate until further in the projectile path.
That's actually really nice.
Like Lucas, I can stand here and dig.
Let me dynamite.
I have so many of it anyway.
Why shouldn't I dynamite?
Can I get rid of freezing vapor with some fireballs?
Ah, it doesn't look like it.
I do wonder if there's a way to get rid of that vapor somehow quick.
Because it is actually kind of annoying.
No, that's ambrosia.
I will take it.
So I'm actually... Okay, look at this.
I'm standing in a pool of it right now.
What prevents me from making like a little hole somewhere?
Put some ambrosia in.
It doesn't even have to be a lot.
And I just stand here.
How is that not completely busted?
There's got to be a drawback somehow, some way.
You know what I mean?
Like... Oh my god.
It shoots fast too.
Oh yeah, baby.
The only problem with this one is that it sets things on fire.
And as we all know, fire is a bad thing.
Oh, that's disappointing.
I thought I saw something in there.
Uh, I think I hurt myself.
Is that confirmed?
Wait, hold on.
I'm actually trying to hurt myself.
Not sure.
I feel like I took damage there.
Maybe not.
Oh, what's this?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Very cool.
Did someone shoot something?
It did shoot something.
You little bastard.
Got a girder here.
That always makes me think of worms.
I loved putting girders in worms.
Call me crazy, but that was the funniest stuff.
Just wall yourself in.
What's happening?
Oh, hello.
Wow, you're not dead yet!
Okay, you're not very...
what do you already call it?
You're very resistant to my wand.
You needed like 15 shots.
I think I've been up here.
Hold on, is this a...?
No, it's a normal teleport.
It's not a short one.
Toxic sludge potion.
No thanks.
Nobody wants that.
Holy shit, that sniper shot.
Oh!
Where are you, man?
I have a laser pointer too, bitch.
I must have hit him there.
Sniper?
I think... I feel like I hear him.
Oh, that's a shotgun, man.
But there's a sniper somewhere.
There he is.
Taken care of.
What?
That was scary.
What do we got?
Oh, no thanks.
This is steel, unfortunately.
See, this is where I could use a black hole.
Dang it.
Let me get in there.
No.
Am I out?
That was weird, I couldn't throw dynamites for a second there.
Okay.
Spells per cast nine.
Wow.
Nah.
Not feeling it.
Oh, polymorphine.
What is happening here?
Snowman.
That's also steel.
Shit.
Oh, ouch.
Wait, I can get up here.
Ah, fuck.
I didn't see he was aiming.
That was bad.
Ah!
He would have missed if I hadn't flown into a shot.
Like a dumbass.
Look at all these wands I'm finding, though.
Yes!
There it is!
I want that so bad.
Yes, please.
Um, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Spells per cast one.
Hell yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Yes, baby.
Yes!
Beautiful stuff.
Oh, that's it?
I thought it was like a huge reservoir of water.
Ah!
Hold on now.
I'm fucking stuck.
Ominous music here.
Oh my god.
Whoa!
Thanks.
Okay, that worked pretty well.
That was sweet.
Crowd control?
Like killing a bunch at the same time here?
AOE?
That's really nice.
See this one?
Suspicious hand.
It's the same symbol as on that statue we saw.
If I have telekinetic kick, I can take that with me.
Maybe I can bring it to that statue if something will happen.
Oh wait, this is the entrance.
I never went west.
Rotten meat.
Oh!
Let's be careful here.
I think that's a frost man.
It's not an electricity man.
It's electricity, I'm not sure.
Hold on, these guys bleed diamonds, but something happened with diamonds.
Did it turn into snow?
Packed snow?
Frozen?
Okay, you're a frost man.
A frost man, no.
Man, I'm having fun with this wand.
It's satisfying to shoot.
Makes me have more confidence with the saw blade orbit or whatever it's called.
Because if that also activates at a certain distance away from you, maybe it's not too bad to use.
And that thing could be sick.
Man, I'm not gonna get through there.
Maybe here.
Oh yeah, much easier.
Hold on, before I go down there.
Uh oh.
I hear electricity.
Where is he?
Okay, it's you.
What's that?
Unstable teleportation potion.
Why is he blocking?
I'm gonna check this wand.
Oh, this wand is really good so far.
Oh, lightning thrower.
That is a lot of fireboats with trigger.
Holy shit.
Do I want that?
I don't think I do.
Sounds crazy, but no.
I mean, the wand kind of sucked anyway.
It was shuffle, all that.
Not a fan.
Whoa, take cover.
Guys, I just remembered dude.
It's Friday.
Cheers everybody.
I love when you forget it and re-remember it.
The best feeling ever.
Hey, you there.
God, this electricity thing is so good against the turrets.
Just insta-kill.
Oh my god, look at this.
Here we go, boy.
Fortune smiles upon us.
And a wand?
Uh oh, I see that in this.
I see that, I see that, I see that.
That was a, that was a bit of a trap there.
What do we got here?
Weakening curse electricity.
Now that could be a great combination with my current, uh, lightning bolt, right?
I think I like it, but I really don't want to give up any of, hold on.
Tell me I have an extra...
Oh man, this is, I really want to keep these.
This thing is nuts.
Ah, why did I, hmm, kind of want to exchange my teleport.
Is that, is that insane?
Castelay.
Oh man.
No, it's not that great.
Let's leave it.
Also, I hear electricity.
There's a guy somewhere.
Oh, cool.
Also, I just got sniped.
Whoa.
Okay, I see you, I see you, I see you.
Show your laser.
I think I got him.
No, I didn't.
No, I, no, I didn't.
I'm on fire.
Here comes the pack.
Bro, this wand is sick.
It actually shoots fast too.
Okay, so the way we deal with this guy is, just do that, I guess.
We have sick range with this, so why not just spam him?
Are you dead?
Vomit?
Wait!
Oh, wait, did Diamond get transformed into Vomit?
Is that what's happening?
Hello?
That's awesome.
Magical temple.
It feels gloomy in here.
I think what that means is enemies have ghosts on them, but I'm still not sure what that means, like actually.
Do you want to explore it though?
I did not see this platform there.
Did he die?
Nope.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Maybe, no, you know what, maybe we'll leave.
Huh?
Let's leave.
Just looking at our HP here, this is a risky move.
It really is.
That Vomit.
Wait, how did I?
Did I just heal?
How did I just heal?
Wait, what?
I was at 40 something, wasn't I?
How did I just heal?
I, I must have looked wrong.
I must have, I must have looked at this four and thought it was in front of the nine.
Weird.
Okay.
Well, don't go that way actually.
Go this way.
Let's see what's over here.
I just got to go down actually.
Okay, we're at the edge.
So wait a minute.
That means our thing is wrong.
Unless it changes.
I got this wrong, I think.
Hold on.
This is, this is, this is wrong.
Let's do, let's shrink this down a bit.
It's more like that.
Remove that one and then do a line.
In fact, move this textile like that for now.
Let me draw a line.
Honestly, maybe it's even like this.
Hold on, not that big though.
Like that.
Because that's what it looks like to me now.
Straight down.
Delete that.
That looks nice.
It's more like that, isn't it?
There we go.
Okay.
That looks better.
Unless this also connects...
No, this is, I think this is more accurate now.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, there's a guy there.
He was hiding, waiting for me.
Thinking I wouldn't see him.
Whoa.
Calm yourself.
Where are you?
Okay.
I see you.
Ah, shit.
I thought I was teleporting there.
Damn it.
Okay.
That works.
68 HP.
What's that?
Brass.
Hmm.
Interesting.
There's a sniper.
I'm just going to shoot off in the distance, hopefully hitting something.
What is he shooting at?
Uh-oh.
This is a bad time.
I'm going to make a little choke point here.
Come to me.
Come up here.
Come on, bitch.
You mad now?
Oh, he's dumb.
He doesn't understand.
Hey, we got to try something here.
This is how we do it.
Look.
Get cheesed, bitch.
No regrets.
This game cheeses me all the time.
I feel it.
Boink.
And there's a chest.
Pass me.
What the hell?
Do we want that?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure I want that.
Never mind.
Oh, man.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look at all that blood.
I wonder how we say a lot in Finnish.
I want to say a lot of blood.
You know?
That was a mix between Italian and Finnish.
Sounded kind of legit.
Rats on fire.
Mayday, mayday.
Man, I'm doing great.
I shouldn't say that.
That's totally jinxing it.
Things are going to go downhill now.
Just because I cursed it.
Oh, I actually really like this laser pointer.
There's a sniper somewhere.
I love the way this ice is animated.
Like when you shoot it, it breaks apart like that.
I have never seen anything like that.
Like this dynamic, you know?
Really is an achievement.
Kiva Skivi.
I guess Kiva means fire then.
Firestone?
Brimstone, maybe.
Oh,
we got to blow it up.
Damn.
That was a huge collection of explosives.
Oh, look at that.
That's what happens when you keep exploring.
You get rewarded.
And boy, does it feel good.
Aha.
That guy's frozen.
I like this one.
I like that one.
Should I take it though?
These are too good.
No, it's not enticing enough.
It just isn't.
Look how fast I'm teleporting to because of the pin pointer.
It's practically instant.
What's in here?
Oh, hold on.
There's a wand.
No, I've been here before.
Yeah, I've been here.
But what's in here?
A snowman.
I'm gonna go further down.
I haven't been down there yet.
Let me keep going over here.
Aha.
Oh,
look at that.
Whoa, I heard you.
Add to sneeze there.
Also, look at my lightning bolt.
It explodes way further away and that's because of my pin pointer.
It speeds the projectile up.
Hey, you're there.
There we go.
No idea what you were up to.
Ethereal meat?
Eat it.
Oh, shit.
I ate the wrong thing.
I got teleported.
That's fine though.
Oh, I'm here.
Okay.
It's not too bad.
There's a wand down there.
Now we're talking.
Like that one.
Ah, shit.
You know what?
Fuck the teleport.
We don't need it.
We can get another one.
That's fine.
I don't want to run with the triplicate bolt again though.
I feel like I've done that so much lately and I kind of want to do something else.
Ah, look at this.
Man, this level is big.
Ah, wait.
I can't get in there.
It's all steel and shit.
There's got to be a way in.
Whoops.
I got a little bit too eager there.
In fact, I am actually kind of low on HP.
Ah, tell me there's a way in.
No way.
Come on.
Shit.
What about if I go around like this?
Whoop.
Damn it.
Maybe from below somewhere.
Maybe there's a small point where there's no metal.
Oh, man.
There's a health in there.
Oh, they're teasing me so bad.
Fuck.
Oh, man.
I mean, listen, there's a chance if I keep exploring that I'll find what you might call it.
Plasma wand.
Right?
And then I can get in.
Probably Copium, but we'll see.
Like, what's that one, right?
What's this?
Oh, you know what?
Dude, I'm going to go through the portal now.
I'm going to take this one with me because there's already lightning bolts on it.
And then I'm going to grab this as well at the same time.
Obviously, I didn't want to do that before because I needed it to fight.
But now I don't, because I'm going through the portal.
I've decided.
I'm coming back later for this here.
In fact, I'm going to write that down.
Otherwise, I will forget it.
Zoom out a bit there.
So we're going to have a...
Oops.
Oh my God.
There was old lines.
No way.
Extra HP in snowy depths.
Close the portal.
There we go.
Move on.
Let's get down into that portal immediately.
Sweet burger.
Very nice.
I have lots of money.
Okay.
Nah, not too enticed by all that.
Faster.
What's this?
Faster wants.
Critical hit plus.
Hmm.
Guys, I'm not enticed.
I'm not feeling it.
Okay.
I've never tried this one, I guess.
I don't know how much more.
But here's the thing.
Even if this set critical hit on every shot, would it be worth... Actually, it would be worth it because critical hit is like five times the damage, no?
Huh.
Maybe that is worth it depending on how much that is.
Let's say it's 50%.
That would roughly be two and a half times more damage.
That is not bad, but that is an assumption.
I don't know how much this is.
I guess I could test it.
Should I really do that or do I...
Oh man.
I don't know.
Oh no, I'm gonna... I believe.
Saving Grace is good.
Uh, one.
No, I want... Yes.
Saving Grace is good.
It's really good.
Okay, let's see what we can make.
Weakening curse on this seems good, but this is a shuffle one, of course.
That's bad.
So this one on that would be kind of dope.
Let me see here.
But my wands kind of suck.
Let's get a better wand.
Let's see.
Do we have any good ones?
They're all fucking shuffled.
This one is not shuffled.
But it sucks.
It's a high spread and everything.
Now this one also sucks because it only has two...
Man, what?
Point two, point five.
Man, I'm not feeling these wands at all.
Hold on.
What if I get rid of this?
And I add... Or should I maybe not focus on the magic bolt?
I feel like now that I have the damage plus, I feel like I should do something with it, you know?
Energy sphere...
Whoa, this one adds crit chance?
Interesting.
I don't know if I should focus on making my main wand a lightning wand or not.
I mean 125 damage, right?
Oh, you know what?
We should definitely make it a lightning wand because look at this.
Oh, how much does it cost?
70 mana?
This one has 247... 242 plus...
Oh, we can definitely... can triple this shit up right here.
Recharge is not that good.
Unfortunately, maybe that's even overkill.
We don't need that much.
Maybe two is enough because then we can add a mana on it.
Like that.
No, that's not good either.
Don't like it.
Triplicate bolts can go on the floor.
And of course I want this target hit by a... So I wonder if that counts with the same projectile that damages for the first time.
If they're gonna check... We can check this.
We can check this.
Let's do it simple here.
Simple, simple, simple.
Just a single shot.
150.
Because... Wait, why 150?
Shouldn't that be 125?
Maybe this does a certain amount of damage in itself.
All right, whatever.
150.
Let's do this.
Okay, so it adds...
Wait, what?
It adds a little bit.
It's 25%.
I'm not sure that works the way I want it to.
I feel like I should do something with this.
0.07.
If I just do something like that...
Like this is gonna do decent damage.
This is like 23 damage per shot.
It's not bad.
Not bad at all, but this one... All right, it does that thing.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Nope.
If anything, I would definitely add more magic bolts to this.
Like in a double or something.
That's not bad, you know?
But we're gonna be going into, I believe, Heezy Base next, so...
We need some damage here, man.
We can't be going around.
We definitely need Circle of Transmogrification.
That's a must.
A show, baby.
Maybe Circle of Shielding would be better in there, in those close quarters?
Huh?
Would be kind of cool.
Kind of want to bring black holes as well.
There's so many things I want to do.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I'm gonna focus on... I think I'm too focused on this damage plus.
I need to not do that, and I need to throw my lightning bolts.
Because that is a surefire fucking one, and I know it works, and it's great.
So what I'm gonna do... I could even throw this on, but that's not gonna do much.
Mana?
Double?
That's solid.
Why is it so slow, though?
Oh, this adds a shit ton of castellae, that's why.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
So maybe...
Maybe that's more damage per second.
I'm not actually sure.
Fuck,
I don't know.
Maybe it's all about that one tap.
You know, fuck everything else.
It's all about the one tap.
Maybe we go three, because we shoot it once.
Ah, we have to wait quite a while.
That's not worth it.
We go two with the mana.
This is good.
This is a decent... this is like 200 something damage.
That's great.
Now, this one is fine.
I like my polymorph.
Then we're gonna have...
Well, we don't have teleports, so that's fine.
So we can instead have Black Hole.
Why not?
And on this one, let's go a little crazy.
Something utility.
We could go for Circle of Shielding.
Just have some fun here.
With some dynamites, maybe.
What could be useful?
Poland does digging.
I should maybe do that.
Let's get this down here.
It's up there.
Actually, these also dig, I guess.
How does this look like?
Not bad.
Dum, dum, dum, dum.
Yeah.
Oh, it's Shuffle.
Fuck!
Dang it, I hate Shuffle.
It's the worst.
Maybe just go with that.
This is my digging.
Yeah.
All right, let's move.
I'm not happy about this.
I feel like it's not very great.
But it is what it is.
Maybe I grab this refresh.
Should I grab the refresh?
Yeah, let's do it.
We have a bunch left anyway, so it's okay.
Nope, let's go.
I have a decent wand here.
Easy base.
I'm back, baby.
Nice, nice, nice.
Hopefully I can find a plasma cutter in here.
I feel like chances of finding one in here is way bigger.
It's always in here I find them.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
That one tap.
Oh, Jesus.
I hit something right in front of me.
I didn't see it.
Why am I taking damage all the time?
Uh-oh.
The added range on it is actually kind of detrimental at times.
Get rid of that.
I'm scared of using it right here.
Oh, but it's okay.
God fucking damn it.
Why did that explode in front of me?
Like the laser clearly went behind it.
I can't trust this fucking laser.
Oh, don't even start with me.
Oh, this is going terribly.
This is not good.
But hold on.
If we can find the animal, maybe there's a chance.
Uh-oh.
That should be on the right somewhere.
Did I mark that on my map?
I did not.
So, so far it's always been in the bottom right.
Let me do that.
Let me make a little note for that.
Do, do, do, do, do.
Something like that.
Maybe I'm wrong, but for now, I'm going to write anvil.
Let's just replace that.
Anvil.
Or smithy, whatever you want to call it.
Let's keep going.
Oh man, there's explosives everywhere and all this metal.
Oh, I may have chosen the wrong weapon for this place.
If I go slow, it's okay, I think.
Like look at that.
That was great.
Same as that.
The one tab is real.
The extra, the extra range.
Nevermind.
I am neutral on that.
I'm neither happy nor sad about it.
It does have its uses.
Like look at that stuff right there.
I have to remember, I still have this.
If I need to dig.
Pheromone?
Oh dude, that's actually something I wanted to try.
I need to find that one ghostbuster that heals the others.
I want to try pheromone on him.
Uh, I should pick that up.
I keep forgetting I have this ambrosia.
You know what?
Let's uh, hold on.
If I make a little...
Look at this!
Like, that's insane.
I just need a little puddle.
Not bad.
Here's the thing.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna put this ambrosia.
Uh, no, wait, not here.
Where did I?
Oh, below me, below me.
That guy is gonna... Oh god, this is a bit scary.
He broke the ice!
Jump!
Jump, you mother... Oh, let's not break the pheromone.
I'm scared of breaking the pheromone here.
This is a big risk.
For my exp... That was close!
That was pretty close.
Up!
Sup guys?
Let me grab it.
Right.
Oh, hold on.
Surprise!
Let's put this down gently.
There we go.
Okay, let's just keep an eye out.
I kind of forgot what they look like.
You are annoying.
There we go.
That works.
Is that lava?
No, it's brass.
Oh, what?
Wrong.
I thought I was shooting this one.
I wanted to mix.
God damn it.
Oh, he has a wand.
Oh, wait, was that the guy?
Shit.
Hold on.
I need to pay attention here.
You there.
Come here.
Also, I'm standing on explosives.
This is...
This can only go wrong.
Let's... How about we get rid of this?
Nope.
Get rid of it.
No, no, no, no.
Yes.
Then we blow it up.
This is gonna blow up for sure.
Come on.
There we go.
Nice.
Sweet.
A bunch of bombs.
Well, I don't really need it.
Not really.
Ah.
Huh.
Got a stone.
Nah.
Not interested.
See, I can't get through here.
That's the issue.
Actually, never mind.
I can.
I have black hole.
But actually, I can get through because there's snow here.
So never mind.
Oh, God.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
I'm a goddamn genius.
He's gonna follow me around.
Yeah.
Heal me.
I thought I was gonna kick that one down to them, but I guess it somehow exploded.
I don't know why, but... No, no.
Don't die.
Here.
Water.
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
You're my buddy now.
Oh.
Dude, pheromone is the new strategy.
That's how we do it, baby.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no.
Don't kill my friend.
Do not.
Hey.
You fuckers.
You shall pay for this.
Fuck you.
You like that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
I'm on fire.
I can't believe I discovered that.
That's amazing.
Oh, this game is incredible.
It keeps surprising you even after like 70 hours.
Actually, more like 75 hours at this point.
Uh, what's up here?
I have totally found a new way to heal.
Hmm.
Suspicious.
Very suspicious that, in fact.
That almost was a disaster.
Guys, I think I was on the brink of death just now.
My heart rate.
Let's calm down.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh, oh.
Okay, check this out.
We're gonna do this.
I gotta be careful because black hole sucks everything in.
So maybe I'll do something like that.
Yes, sir.
That's what I'm... Actually, look, it's being converted to water on the way down.
Oh, I can't get up there.
That's frozen.
Yeah, I'm not liking the look on that.
Yes.
You fucker.
I'm so confused.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I could use black hole here, but I'm not gonna because I have this.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
It's got a little sketchy.
Okay, we gotta be on the lookout for those guys now.
Like, we really gotta be on the lookout.
Do not kill everything on site.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Mix, mix, mix, mix.
There we go.
What's that?
More pheromone?
Uh, maybe actually.
Let's just not take it yet.
Did I hear a portal down there?
Oh yeah, I did.
There's a portal right.
So let's check.
Maybe I'm wrong.
No, I'm not.
Look, here it is.
Always in the bottom right.
Always.
Uh, shuffle, boo.
I don't like it, I don't think.
Nope.
Pinpoint of light.
No, thanks.
You can keep it, bro.
And now I have another slot for pheromone.
Thank you.
Pheromone, new best friend.
Friendship ended with, uh, I don't even know.
What do we got in here?
Bombs.
Yeah.
Let's not mess with that.
I see enemies in there.
No, never mind.
That was a force field.
Kind of want to get in there.
Let it flow.
In fact, do this and mix it up while it comes down.
That way we make a lot of water.
And we actually kind of need water.
I'm gonna kill that guy while that is draining.
I'm gonna just make my way through here.
Uh-oh, that was a bit scary what I did there.
Shit.
That hurt a lot.
Okay, be on the lookout for these guys.
Healers, where are you?
Fucking healing busters.
That's a shotgun, man.
Oh my god, he actually hit me.
This bastard.
Nice.
That's a bit sketch.
Oh, he died.
Haha.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Wait, what?
Extra max HP?
There's a heart down there, look.
You can't see it, but it's there.
Uh-oh, oh no.
I almost killed myself.
Oh man, how am I gonna get in there?
I guess I could water it.
I need more water though.
Wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
No, I don't have an idea.
Never mind.
That idea was bad.
Bad idea.
Ah, nice.
Okay.
Oh god, here comes the gang.
Peek-a-boo.
It's ogre.
We're done.
We're gonna find a portal immediately.
I know where there is one.
We're heading back.
Nope, we're done.
We are done here.
Please don't kill me.
Oh, man.
This is not good.
This ain't good, bro.
There's a portal somewhere down here.
In fact, I hear it, I think.
No, wait, that was something else.
Yeah, here it is.
Go, go.
Holy shit.
That was scary.
God damn.
Hey, is that?
Hey, there we go.
Plasma cutter, my beloved.
And all kinds of crazy shit there.
Oh, small teleport.
Very nice.
And then we have the last cannon, revenge tentacle, and I'm tempted to re-roll.
Do I want to spend, I mean, the teleport there.
I can always come back and buy this later, right?
But so again, then again, I can always come back and re-roll these two, but I'm gonna, no, I'm gonna.
Oh, I thought this was fire immunity.
Nevermind.
Invisibility.
I'm taking that, thank you.
Thank you very much.
And then I come back later, I guess.
So far, so good.
Don't want to change anything.
Not quite yet.
I think I'm fine the way it is.
Go.
Whoops.
I keep remembering, or misremembering.
I don't have teleport right now.
I changed it.
Okay, back in the jungle.
Let's kick some ass, huh?
There we go.
I need to be extra careful with this lightning.
Like, I can't shoot it when I'm not entirely sure that I'm not gonna be standing in front of a wall.
Oh yeah, I'm invisible.
Uh-oh, he's not dead.
Oh man, it's actually kind of hard to hit these guys.
Hold on, do we have healers in here?
Not that I need one right now, but let's keep an eye out.
Oh, I'm immune to these guys.
Fantastic.
Fantastico.
I'm immune to these guys as well.
Proggies, also immune.
Should we go tripping again?
I see mushrooms.
That would be fun.
I gotta water that.
Because then we mix and then we grab all the water in our bottle.
Dum-da-dum-da-dum.
Oh, hello.
Doink.
Wait, shit.
That works.
I'm gonna get high.
Let's do it.
Do we have enough to get high?
Okay.
Oh yeah, come on, come on, come on.
I don't even know why I'm doing it, just fun.
You know, love getting high in Noita.
Eat that, eat all of this.
I don't think we can get high enough.
We need to be tripping balls for this to work.
There we go.
Oh man, I'm just out here looking for my next fix.
Unaware of my surroundings.
What is that?
Flemable gas?
That's weird.
Why is that in there?
Let's go further down.
Hello, sir.
Oh, you're not dead.
Oh God, man.
Everything is fucked.
Holy... Oh, one time.
Sweet.
Sweet mayonnaise.
Oh no, it's another one of... Oh boy, I can get in there later, because I found a plasma cutter.
I can go get it when I have enough money.
That's the plan.
We gotta eat more mushrooms.
Oh, I see a bunch of mushrooms up there.
Hold on, grab these.
And we go up here.
Eat all of that.
We eat these.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
I'm also eating all kinds of other shit right now.
That makes me puke.
Am I high enough?
Not yet.
What's that?
No, thanks.
Actually, wait a minute.
That's a lot of mana.
I gotta say, what's that?
Show me.
Uh-oh.
Oh, I'm invisible.
That's why I didn't see me.
Of course.
Did he die?
Man, I'm running out of mushrooms.
Come on.
Mushroom me.
Oh.
Oh, but wait, we're immune.
We're immune.
Everything's fine.
Somehow the spiders look even creepier when you're tripping.
I don't even know how it's possible, but it is possible.
He's not taking a lot of damage here.
Oh man, that is just... God, I hate it.
Oh, it's raining fire.
Oh no, I'm poisoned.
How are you not dead, sir?
Jesus Christ.
I hit you like three times with that lightning shit.
Okay, we're coming down from the trip.
There we go.
Nice.
I need to upgrade my weaponry.
It's not enough.
Oh, nice.
Cool.
There's extra health hanging out there.
Ouch.
I kind of want peace with gods.
And then I want the plasma cutter, and then I want to go up top again, because there's a lot of things I wrote down that I want to go back and grab.
There's all kinds of shit.
Another spider there.
Let's see what's on this.
Hold on.
Is that?
No, it's not.
Oh man.
What?
I got him?
Ow.
I thought I missed that.
Okay.
That looks really bad.
Holy crap, the whole gang.
Come here.
The ultimate choke point.
Don't be greedy.
Don't get the gold.
Don't be dumb.
Ow.
My guy has sick aim.
Hello.
Ice ball.
I like it.
Thanks.
I do enjoy that.
Now I have to remember.
Okay, cool.
Look at that.
Spider in the wall.
It's actually kind of bad that I don't have a proper weapon right now.
Holy shit.
How are you not dead, sir?
What was that?
A mine?
Ah crap.
Oh no.
That's what I have to say about that.
I know, very insightful stuff.
Oh no, I can't take through that.
Ah shit.
I need my other wand.
Maybe I'll come back for this.
I mean, I guess I can actually just go back and deposit this wand up here.
I'm gonna do that.
Ah, the best way to get back up there.
In fact, I need to buy some wands up there anyway.
No, but I do that later.
Oh, I can't change my wands though.
Ah fuck, how do I get out of here?
Oh, that's annoying.
I have to go all the way around?
Crap.
Give me this.
No, uh, go around here.
Oh, that's an annoying path.
Can I even... Oh no!
There's no way I'm finding my way back here.
There's just no way.
We need tinker with wands everywhere.
Stat.
Oh my god, what a detour.
What's that?
Slimy yank.
A horta.
I hurt the horta.
Can't get in there.
I could go tripping.
I don't think I have enough mushrooms.
I need water.
Sweet.
Hey, look at this!
Something... There's always something below it.
Maybe not this time.
Ah, look at that!
There we go.
He's still not dead.
And I'm poisoned.
Aw, I hate these guys so much!
Fuck off, please.
I'm actually gonna die to these guys.
I kid you not.
They're gonna be my end.
Is he dead?
He's not dead.
That's unreal.
He's still not dead.
Are you fucking kidding me?
How are you not dead?
I'm gonna die.
Holy crap!
I think this guy is somehow resistant to electricity.
There's just no other explanation.
There's no way.
He has some kind of modifier on him, for sure.
Oh wait, can I even get back up?
Okay, thanks.
Wait, can I even dig through?
Yes, I can.
Wait, what?
Ah, freezing paper.
Perfect.
Don't fall on me.
This one right here gets to stay right there.
Let's see.
Ah, you know what?
I may just actually get it.
The one itself is not bad either.
Yo, that's... that's not bad.
That's really good.
Now we just gotta not die.
Oh, oh my god.
Thank you.
It was close that I missed that one.
I kind of don't want to grab my other wand I had.
I just want to leave it and move on with this, because this is my new digging wand.
Don't get hit, don't get hit, don't get hit.
Nice.
I am invisible.
I have to remember this.
No, not.
Oh, hold on.
It's the big guy again.
At least he doesn't have poison.
I'm grateful for that.
That was a perfect hit.
Again, perfect hit.
You worry of mines.
Oh, did he already die?
Oh, there's a mine.
How did that not explode?
That was a straight hit.
I am invisible.
Oh,
turn this into water.
I have to remember, don't switch to my other wand now, because that is a plasma wand and that could kill me if I'm not careful.
Oh no, not this guy again.
He's fleeing.
He's fleeing the scene.
Hold on.
I'm scared of that plant.
It's gonna block my shot.
You know what?
Let's leave him.
Let's not tangle with that guy.
I'm tempted to just go through the portal because of my HP.
It's bad, guys.
I'm low.
But the issue is, I don't really have any good wands.
Oh man, hold on.
There we go.
Oh my god, this digging wand is really good.
I hate this.
It's bad.
All right, let's leave.
I don't feel great about this.
I really don't.
What do we got?
What's that?
Deadly heal.
No more knockback.
Stronger.
I mean, I'm tempted to take that.
Especially because I don't have mana to re-roll this shit at all.
So yeah.
Why not?
Let's do it.
Heart's bestow more mana.
And I don't have enough of that, unfortunately.
Damn it!
Well.
Well, well, well.
Let's see this wand here.
100 mana max.
Maybe we can make something actually good out of this.
Also, I left behind a damage plus.
We have to remember that.
Maybe we go with... maybe it's energy sphere time.
I don't really have much else to work with.
Energy sphere.
And no, hold on.
Is that a good idea?
Can I buy anything here?
Could buy this, but I don't like that.
What's that?
Tiny ghost.
Man, I don't know.
Maybe we just make a better electricity wand.
So... oh, do we even have mana for that?
Seven?
No, we don't have mana.
Oh, shit.
No, that's not gonna work.
Crap, man!
What we could do is add this here.
Add this.
Well, that costs 50 mana though.
That's bad.
That's really bad.
I mean, I feel like I'm out of options here.
I just gotta go like... No, you know what?
No.
Put this here.
Let me move on.
We just gotta find something.
It is what it is, man.
This is a shitty situation we're in.
A lot of HP, but no damage.
This is a disaster.
Honestly, I'm kind of looking forward to dying.
Just so I can start over and have a better run, because this is just... Yeah, look at this.
This is already terrible.
God damn it.
I didn't realize that could electrify me from that range.
Uh-oh.
Come up here.
That works.
Okay.
Oh!
That was scary.
I went into the water with my wand.
Caught myself in time there.
That was scary.
Okay, you know what?
I have an idea.
We're gonna do something.
We're gonna anger the gods now.
I don't care.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
I don't give a shit.
Oh, you know what?
Let me get ready.
I feel like this run is kind of ripped anyway, so whatever.
We're going all out here.
Wait, why is this... Oh, because it collapsed, of course.
I'm gonna use this to my advantage.
Hopefully it won't fall on me.
Are you gonna be mad?
Huh, gods?
You like that?
Hold on, do I have a way to kill him?
Uh, circle of transmogrification, maybe?
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
We're gonna try that on him.
This is the way.
I'm going back up, baby.
I need to not fear these fucking gods, because, man, I'm so scared of them.
And it's changing everything I do, you know, because of that.
I need to face my fears.
Oh,
I'm almost drowning, I would say.
There's the portal.
Wait, why is the gods not angry?
Hello?
Let me actually just anger him, just to get it over with.
Why are you... why are you not angry?
Maybe... okay, maybe it doesn't work anymore after it's already collapsed, huh?
Maybe the god is like, ah, whatever, that temple is done anyway.
That's what I think.
I'm so scared of hitting myself with this.
Here we go, we're back.
And that guy is also back.
Cool.
All right, what's the plan?
Hold on, what is the plan?
Maybe the plan is to... you know what?
Okay, so I consider this run already fucked, you know, so whatever.
Maybe I'll go up top and try to go back to the ancient laboratory and fuck up that boss.
Maybe electricity is just what the doctor ordered, I don't know.
But we're gonna try.
We're gonna try again.
You know, but I'm gonna explore just a bit more here.
Maybe I'll find a good wand.
But the issue is, even if I find a wand, I won't actually be able to change it.
It's actually a disaster.
Okay, hold on, new plan.
I just realized something.
This is what we have to do.
We actually have to go back down and then invisibility our way through the entire level now.
Make yourselves at home, guys.
All right.
Cool, I guess.
How's he not dead?
Is he drowning?
What the fuck?
What the hell is going on here?
Wait, where am I right now?
Oh, wait, I have money for this.
Let's try it.
I protect all that at first, deals damage, then heals over time.
How much?
Oh, I can't use it.
Oh, of course.
Shit.
Whatever.
So we're going to invisibility our way through, then we're going to splint to sell this.
And let me just get rid of this guy first.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my Lord.
Oh, man.
This is a bad spot.
Oh, shit.
This is really bad.
Get it.
Oh, wow.
Okay, invisibility.
Come on.
De-stain me.
Dry my clothes.
Oh, come on.
Oh, hold on.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Fucking fly, you fool.
Oh, no.
It's over.
This is over.
I can't... I'm dead.
I'm dead.
I can't fucking...
Go!
Fucking de-stain me, bitch.
There's stains everywhere.
I can't not get stains.
What is this, man?
Get up here.
I want to kick you to death.
That's right.
Fuck you.
Come on, get rid of it.
Oh, my Lord.
Here we go.
Don't touch anything.
Splintacil mode engaged.
Oh, no.
There's blood everywhere.
That's a mate.
Shit!
I ran out of fucking levitation.
De-stain me.
There we go.
Huh?
He switched places with me.
It's that guy.
Oh, God.
Just do it.
Whatever.
I'm invisible.
This is a disaster.
How do I go down?
Do I go in there?
I have a black hole at my disposal.
Don't get near me.
I need to kill this guy.
I need to kill that guy for sure.
There we go.
Okay.
Black hole time.
Oh, no.
I'm completely stained.
Of course, I went in the water.
It makes sense, but still.
De-stain me.
Come on.
Maybe I have to fly around a bit more, you know?
Get some air in my cape.
That works pretty well.
Nice.
Just go down.
Down, down, down.
As far down as it goes.
Of course.
Oh, my Lord.
Oh.
This is sketchy.
Can I go through enemies without them?
And they're okay with it?
I have flashbacks to other situations right now where I did that.
Okay.
I can go through them.
We're fine.
This is fine.
This is not the way, though.
This is not the way, unfortunately.
Let's try this way.
What the fuck?
Come on.
Down, down, down.
Does that stain me?
What is that?
Confetti?
Portal!
This is it.
Go!
Oh, man.
The prices, though.
What?
What is that?
Oh, man.
It's damage.
Come on.
What's that?
I don't like any of this, guys.
It's over.
It's fucking over.
Oh, man.
You know what I could do?
I could try and go for a win.
What if I just stealth my way through this fucking place again?
I could do it.
Hmm.
I could do that.
Hold on.
Anger the gods.
Fuck your temple.
Nobody likes your shitty-ass temple.
Come here.
Oh, no.
I collapsed it.
I'm an idiot.
That's exactly what I didn't want to happen.
Yeah, well.
Does it get any worse from here?
I don't think so.
I really don't think so.
Splint the cell time.
Let's go.
Just go.
I don't give a shit about anything right now.
We just go.
What is the... Okay, this is going up.
We're not going down.
This is bad.
At least I don't have to be afraid of walking through these enemies anymore.
I'm okay with that.
Okay, so this is not the path.
Let's go south.
In fact, I should have used the spell refresh to get more black holes.
I just realized.
That would have been the play.
Oh, get up here.
Sure.
Further down.
Just keep going.
Ah, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Right, the traps see me.
Okay, we're invisible.
I mean, I have a lot of HP.
It's not actually too bad.
It's just, you know...
What?
Maybe that force field sees me too.
Whatever that force field is.
Why is everything... what's happening?
Jesus Christ, what's happening?
Don't come in here.
Do not come in here.
What is... worm blood?
Oh, I'm gonna be stained.
How am I not stained?
Wait, maybe... can you get stained by worm blood?
Oh, worm blood doesn't stain you?
Look!
Ambrosia?
I already have ambrosia.
Yo, that's awesome.
It doesn't stain you at all.
That's interesting.
That's good to know, actually.
Very nice.
Very cool.
In fact, I should have ate some of that worm blood, I guess.
Oh, no.
Ah, fuck.
Kill him, kill him.
Let's get through here.
That's wood.
That's fine.
Get invisible.
There we go.
And let me go left.
I have a feeling.
That guy just decided to turn into a bunch of gold for me.
Thanks.
I appreciate it, brother.
What is that?
Meat of an innocent creature.
Is it following me?
What's happening?
Get away.
Ah, the trap sees me.
Oh, no.
Does he know I'm here?
Oh, he can sense me.
He's definitely following me.
Oh, no.
How do I get...
Open up.
The FBI.
Wait, does that attack count as melee?
The purple shit.
I feel like I just blocked that.
Oh, no.
I'm invisible.
It's fine.
Let's go.
Oh, they're killing each other?
That's perfectly fine with me.
Uh, how am I gonna get down?
Where is down even?
Shit.
Uh, oh, no.
Maybe over here.
Okay, this looks good.
Yes.
Here we go.
Enter the laboratory.
The laboratory.
Yeah, I can't buy any of this.
I don't have the money.
Oh, come here, buddy.
Yeah, come here.
Come here.
Come here, you.
You know you want to come here.
Come on.
Hey, buddy.
I'm not kidding.
Come here.
There we go.
The music instantly stops.
Yep.
Ooh.
Fire him.
I'm taking that.
So here's the thing.
I may as well heal now, I think, because this is actually the last opportunity I get, and also that.
So, what should I do before this?
It deals damage and heals over time, but I can't really use it on myself, right?
Let's test it.
Ah, I need to find some way to make it shoot into me, right?
Yeah, whatever.
So maybe what I want to do is... I don't even know.
I don't have a lot of... If this doesn't work on the boss, there's just no way, right?
If it does, it's hilarious.
And I love it.
Maybe not have this.
We could probably use something else there.
Maybe some dynamite.
Who knows?
Maybe that will come in handy.
Dynamite with more damage?
Why not?
Probably won't make a difference, honestly.
Fireball orbit?
Nah, let's not do that.
Actually, hold on!
I'm immune to fire!
Fire is my friend.
Actually kind of insane that I'm immune to fire.
Alright, let's go.
Let's see if we can do this.
Wish me luck!
Wish me luck, people!
Let's see what happens.
Oh, wait!
I have... I have Ambrosia!
Let's try and do this smart!
I have an idea, I have an idea.
Is he just gonna appear?
I don't remember what exactly... No, no, I have to click on this, I think.
Our matter.
Oh, man, what the fuck.
Oh, the way he's... Okay, hold on.
Here's the plan.
We're gonna... Watch this.
Oh!
Oh my god!
Hold on.
Oh-ho!
Lolo, lolo, lolo!
We're gonna make a... We're gonna run a bath!
We're gonna run a little bath here.
And then... You know what?
I'm not fucking done!
In case we end up over here...
Shit.
That was my last... God damn it!
Uh, here's what I'm gonna do.
Bloop!
And another bloop here.
And we're gonna bloop up here.
And we're gonna bloop here.
And one bloop... Maybe right here.
Alright, let's try!
Call me Silma!
Well, okay then.
Yeah, that's...
That was... Yeah, okay!
Fair!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's fine!
Hey, look at the total amount of deaths!
Nice!
Cheers, everybody!
That was fun, though.
That was a funny death.
I'm gonna write 69 and then...
Nice.
There we go.
Okay!
Again, again, again!
More, more, more, more, more, more!
By the way, I realized I should have started the game by standing in the fucking ambrosia like I planned.
I don't know why I instinctively jumped up.
I just saw the projectiles and I was like...
I gotta dodge!
You know, like a fucking caveman, I panicked.
At least we start with a nice weapon here.
Energy Sphere.
And we have... Is that blood?
Pheromone.
You know what?
Speaking of pheromone.
We should be trying pheromone on more enemies.
Just because of what we discovered last run.
Which was big, by the way.
That is a big discovery.
A very big one.
Thank you.
Whoa!
Wow, that was close!
That was pure luck that I didn't just die there or like, get hit.
What's that?
Meat.
Let's eat it.
Wait, oil?
One.
Thanks.
Ah!
Oh, look at this stuff!
Ooh, all kinds of stuff is happening here.
I'm intrigued.
Ah,
that's gonna take a while.
Ah, come on.
You know what?
Maybe I just bomb this right here.
And then this also burns.
Man, talk about hitting a bunch of flies with one hit.
You know, I feed two birds with one scone.
They're gonna burn alive, that's fine.
Burn in hell, bitches.
Actually, all that gold.
Oh, no.
All right, whatever.
That's gonna release the cloud.
No?
Oh, wait, the connection is broken.
That's why it doesn't do it.
Le connection ela broken.
That was horrible.
What is all this toxic shit?
Like, come on.
How about we get a little less of that?
Hamis?
Another Hamis.
Uh-oh.
How about poison?
You like this?
Well, that's a slow-ass projectile.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that actually worked really well.
Yeah, I don't dare take that.
That's no, no, no, no, no.
Bad idea.
Oh, he died in the lava.
Oh, careful.
Actually, there's water there.
I may take it.
Pheromone, though.
Hmm.
Now, I need any water.
I need water.
Do you wonder why or what exactly it does when I have pheromone on me?
Maybe it reduces the aggression of the enemies.
You know?
Like, I may not be their friend, but at least I'm not an enemy straight up, you know?
I'm just some random dude out for a walk.
But they still hate the dudes out for a walk, you know?
Don't get me wrong.
It's just...
We're not deathly enemies.
Shotgun, dude.
There we go.
One tap with the energy sphere.
Uh-oh.
Man.
I'm gonna come up here.
I'm gonna use poison on you.
Oh, my God!
Disaster struck immediately.
Decided to jump up into me.
Wow.
This game, man.
It fucks with you.
Oh, shit.
Why are there so many of them?
Like, what's going on here?
Look, another one over there, too!
The hell?
That guy died, at least.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm playing this terribly, man.
There's nothing else to say.
This is just insanity.
It wasn't even worth it, man.
I didn't even get that much gold out of it.
You wanna get that gold?
So much blood.
Acceleration?
I can't believe I still haven't killed the first boss!
Like, what the hell?
The first boss is wild, man!
I really gotta get on that.
And I guess he somehow intended to be killed...
like, when you're here.
Which blows my mind a little bit.
There's just no way.
Or maybe he's not intended for that.
But why would he be here, you know?
Hmm.
Uh, okay.
Oil?
Blow it up!
I thought there was a path through there.
This has been terrible.
I haven't found a single wand, no health, and I only found a million of those fire dudes.
Can I?
Yes, I can.
No, I can't.
Ah!
Ah, fuck you.
That works.
Takes a while, but it works.
Anything up here?
Thank you.
Actually, 450 gold is not bad at this time.
I actually did get a lot of gold.
So at least I'm gonna have a good amount of money for this shop.
Did you see it skip?
I love it when it skip.
That was a sick shot, actually.
He's on fire.
And he died.
Uh-oh.
Do not walk into that.
Oh, another one!
What is this, man?
This is the hardest hemisphere ever.
Holy shit!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Oh my god, 8 HP, yeah, we're out of here.
Where's the exit?
I missed.
I hear the portal.
It's right down there, I think.
Yep, here we are.
Any enemies?
Okay, go!
Sick!
Bunch of money.
Not bad.
What do we got?
We have got... kind of want that.
Plasma Kutair!
Oh, that's awesome.
This is a great start.
Oh, homunculus.
Faster movement.
Projectile duplication.
No.
Nope.
We re-roll those.
Contact damage.
Extra item and hold...
no.
Extra life.
I guess this only works once, obviously.
Yeah, it says one off.
I mean, I guess it does save me, but it feels wasted when it's like...
I could have something proper here, you know?
Hmm.
Maybe this one is good.
Extra item in Holy Mountain.
But like, look at this.
Getting one more here, is that really good?
I don't know if it is.
If it said, guarantee at least one, like, really good item in Holy Mountain, now that would be intriguing.
I'm actually gonna take this.
I choose to respawn with more HP if I die.
Just try it.
Try it out, man.
All seeing eye, I want that.
Let's go with some gig at this projectiles.
No fear this time, no fear.
I'm gonna get that one.
I'm gonna get... that's it.
That's it.
I mean, it's scary.
Oh my, that is actually...
Yikes.
That's kind of scary, isn't it?
That is really scary.
I really wish I had one more wand here.
I guess I don't need this right now.
The damage I need right now is...
No, you know what?
We're rocking that.
Fuck it.
No fear.
Let's have some fun.
And you know what else?
I fear not the gods.
Nope.
Hold on, I need to be ready.
Maybe the gig at this projectile is my key here.
I wonder if I can trigger him in some other way than over there, because he's gonna appear here, right?
So if I trigger over here...
What can I do to anger him?
Let's go up here and dig here.
Let's just make a path up.
Are you mad, bro?
He's not mad yet?
No!
Okay, he's mad, he's mad.
Fuck, that scared me.
Come here, come here, come here.
Okay, okay.
This thing is more danger than fucking good.
Oh, it's bouncing off his shield, it's useless!
Oh no!
It's bouncing off his shield!
Hold on, maybe I can plasma him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, not bad, not bad.
Oh, I'm gonna die here for sure.
Come on.
Get this, get this, fucker.
Come on!
Oh, he's bleeding a lot of shit.
Oh, I'm so dead here.
What the fuck is going on?
How are you not dead?
There we go.
Sit the fuck down.
This is my holy mountain.
That's right, no fear.
Fuck you.
I'm digging my way out over here.
Goddamn.
That was some duel right there.
And now I can get back here and edit my wand.
Fuck you.
I don't fear the gods.
In fact, you fear me.
Probably not, but...
Oh, you know what?
Maybe this is not the thing to use in here because wow, that thing is just bouncing towards me more than anything else.
Maybe we don't do that, huh?
Maybe we go for a good old energy sphere, with an extra energy sphere on top.
For good measure.
Better.
Not bad.
Okay, let's rock and roll.
Rock and roll time.
We have water, we have...
acceleration.
So here's the thing.
We're almost dead.
We don't fear the gods anyway.
What's this?
No.
No, I didn't even notice I died.
Oh, no.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh, well.
I was about to say, at least I have, but I don't.
Shit!
Okay.
It's fine.
Yeah, I think we're gonna get out of here.
We gotta get out of here.
Even though it pains me to say it.
Like, when you start to...
Oh my god!
Yeah, we gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go.
Oh my, there's so many enemies.
Come to me, come to me, come to me.
This is a good spot.
Too much fire for my taste.
We're gonna find the portal right now and head out immediately.
It sucks, because when you're in this position where you rush the portal...
I feel like the run is already over.
Like, that's when you start to not be able to come back from it, you know?
That's when shit goes wrong.
Oh, he hit the other guy!
Amazing.
I gotta get past these guys, though.
I gotta, I gotta, you know?
I gotta, I gotta!
I just, I gotta.
No, I'm gonna die here, for sure.
It's over, man.
Too many enemies.
Oh, man.
Like, the tiny amount of poison, and I'm gone.
Holy shit!
Uh oh, uh oh, uh oh.
Holy mountain, holy mountain, holy mountain!
Holy mountain!
No!
Wow!
I forgot about you, I forgot about you, I'm sorry!
Oh no!
Okay.
Come here.
Do you like rocks?
Whoops.
Oh, he didn't like rocks, it seems.
What is he doing?
Is he killing the fish?
What a menace.
Ugh!
That's for you!
Oh, the rocks are getting absorbed!
No!
That sucks.
God damn it.
I hate the gods.
I want peace with the gods, man.
I don't know, for some reason I thought...
I kind of forgot that he would be at every holy mountain after that.
I thought it was specific to the one you angered, you know?
God damn it.
I mean, I knew it wasn't like that.
I knew that it would be everyone, but I didn't remember in the moment.
And now I'm left with swamp.
That's all I got.
I played Noida for four and a half hours and all I got was a bottle of swamp.
I'm bathing in it.
Actually, I do gotta stop now.
It's getting a little late.
And also...
There's prey coming out for those that are following that.
Let me switch it over.
There we go.
You know what?
I'm actually happy about this one today because we learned some really interesting stuff, you're right?
The healing in Heezy Base.
That's important.
The fact that I can always prepare pheromone for that later on, that's gotta mean a lot.
Right?
That's a big discovery.
And I also almost beat the game again, I guess.
I mean, not really.
I didn't really do anything to the boss, but you know, I was almost there.
So it was a decent run, I guess.
It was a sick discovery, man.
I feel like I didn't play very well today, though, compared to normal.
I think I was too impatient a lot of the time.
Epic battle at the end.
Yeah, man.
You had an eight hour run yesterday.
You died but accomplished your goal, so it's fine.
Oh, well, in that case, awesome.
Good job.
I really liked the last run.
It was different.
And I sort of felt you were getting into a groove.
You know what?
I think I am.
I need to stop being fearful of the...
So here's the thing.
I need to find out what the gods' weakness is.
You know, like, just a general idea of the power level I need to be at to comfortably take them on.
That's what I need to figure out.
Because if I can do that, then the world is my oyster, right?
I feel like that's such an important thing.
I died inside when you threw the Tinker Everywhere run from last time by casting the A Million Explosions one.
Yeah, that one was weird.
Honestly, I looked at it.
I looked at all the spells and I thought, okay, none of this can really kill me, I don't think.
In one hit, at least.
And it was shuffle, right?
There's a bunch of shit on that.
All kinds of random stuff.
So chances were quite low that something would happen.
And if something would happen, that it would kill me.
Because I had like 300 something HP, right?
I feel like that was very unlucky.
All things considered.
And, you know, if you get the Experimental Wands perk, you gotta commit to it, you know?
You gotta experiment.
You're a pretty shitty test pilot if you refer to a fly the newest planes.
I literally died yesterday from a random explosion spell on a new wand I missed.
Oh, that sucks.
That's some... that sucks, man.
Hopefully it wasn't too far into your run.
If only I knew.
What?
Oh, 700.
I was about to say 70?
That's not a lot.
700 though, that's quite a chunk.
I still can't believe that one run where I had like 1500 HP.
That was wild.
I guess it was a crazy coincidence that I also found the extra HP for every heart.
And I got the 50% extra HP at a nice time, you know?
We had 5000?
Holy smokes.
You guys are nuts.
I like that everyone is playing it too right now.
It's quite cool.
Okay, so I'm gonna raid someone immediately.
Let's see who's streaming right now.
I'm gonna go on same category.
I gotta get out of here.
Who is doing things?
I'm just gonna raid someone who's playing Noita as well.
I think it's quite fitting when you're playing the game.
How about a dry Dutch guy who needs to scratch his Noita itch?
I know that feeling.
I'm gonna send you over.
Guys, thank you so much for watching and subscribing and watching.
It's super cool that you're here experiencing the game along with me.
I'm gonna upload the Prey Vod now and have fun with that.
And I hope you have a wonderful weekend.
I'll see you next time, okay?
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.